welcome to category 5 technology TV what
카테고리 5 기술 TV에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
you're about to experience is a free
당신은 경험할 것이 자유 롭습니다.
worldwide interactive broadcast from
에서 전 세계 양방향 방송
Ontario Canada we broadcast live every
온타리오 캐나다 우리는 매일 생방송으로 방송합니다.
tuesday at seven p.m. eastern time get
화요일 오후 7시 동부 시간에 도착
your questions in join the community
커뮤니티 가입에 대한 질문
chat room at triple w category 5 TV or
3 인실 카테고리 5 TV 또는
email us at live at category 5 TV and
카테고리 5 TV에서 실시간으로 이메일을 보내고
now let's begin here's your host Rob a
이제 시작하자. 너의 주인 Rob a가 있네 .
Ferguson welcome to the show is category
퍼거슨 감독의 쇼에 오신 것을 환영합니다
5 episode number 253 nice to see you
만나서 좋은 5 에피소드 번호 (253)
nice to see everyone yes i'm in a while
모두를 만나서 반가워요. 예, 잠시만 요.
i'm doing good husband number of weeks
나는 좋은 남편의 수주를하고있다.
I'm okay yeah it's been a while good
나는 괜찮아, 그래, 오랫동안 좋았어.
summer yes and I'm in a great summer I
여름 예 그리고 나는 위대한 여름에 있어요.
am turned 18 right after celebrate after
축하 후 바로 18 세가된다.
exams i graduated with honors and when
시험을 치렀으며 언제 졸업 했습니까?
you go in rats buddy yeah and now I'm
너는 쥐 친구 야, 네, 나는 지금이야.
dad must be proud oh yeah I thought I
아빠는 자랑스러워해야합니다. 예.
just gonna cry at my graduation yeah but
내 졸업식 때 울 뿐이 네.
also after that I checked out the
그 후에도 나는
university I was going to it looks
나는 거기에가는 대학이 보인다
pretty cool like it'll be AI qual Humber
꽤 멋진 AI AI Humber가 될거야.
and then now for the rest of summer I'm
그리고 나서 나머지 여름 동안 나는
working as a prep cook at the della
델라 에서 준비 요리사로 일하고있다.
wanna in and honey harbour we were we
우리가 있었으면 하 고 꿀 항구에 싶습니다.
were talking before the show so now
지금 쇼 전에 말하고 있었어.
anyone who wants to you know go go meet
너를 알고 싶어하는 사람은 누구나 만나러 간다.
Erica now you know how we were talking
에리카, 이제 우리가 어떻게 말하고 있는지 알지.
about the show when I was younger I
내가 어렸을 때의 쇼에 관해서.
worked at Muskoka woods up
Muskoka 숲에서 일했다.
north of here in Muskoka obviously and
분명히 Muskoka에서 북쪽으로
and and I were in the camp and I stayed
그리고 나는 캠프에 있었고 나는 머물렀다.
there all summer long it's just a riot
여름 내내 오랫동안 폭동을 일으켰다.
so but now we had access to the fridge
그래서 지금 우리는 냉장고에 접근 했다.
in such a way that they would they would
그들이 그런 식으로
roast like these massive carcasses of
이 거대한 시체와 같은 로스트
meat if you're vegetarian I'm sorry this
고기가 네가 채식주의 자라면 이건 미안해.
is going to get very graphic these
이것들을 아주 잘 보여줄 것입니다.
things were massive and they would they
물건은 방대했고 그들은했다.
would serve it to the guests at the camp
캠프에 참석 한 손님들에게 제공 할 것입니다.
and then whatever was left in the fridge
그리고 나서 냉장고에 남겨진 것은 무엇이든
it's like okay we'll cut off a piece and
좋아. 우리가 조각을 잘라내어
take it home with you because it's just
그냥 있기 때문에 당신과 함께 집에 가져
gonna go bad this is wild that was the
나빠질거야 .
best part of the summer right there was
바로 거기에 여름 최고의 부분
the meat well you're working in the
네가 일하고있는 고기 잘
kitchen yeah like I've never worked in a
부엌 에서 일한 적 없어요.
kitchen before so I was very clueless on
전에 부엌은 아주 우둔 했어.
my first day and but you know like I had
나의 첫날. 그러나 내가 알았던 것처럼 당신은 알고있다.
a lot of people who are helping me out
많은 사람들이 저를 사람을 돕고있다
and I'm just like I you prepare like
그리고 나는 너처럼 준비하고있어.
salads and all kind of stuff but the
샐러드와 모든 종류의 재료가 있지만
same time pretty much whenever I like
내가 좋아할 때마다 같은 시간
something that I'm making it put it side
내가 그것을 만들고있는 무엇인가 그것을 옆에 둔다.
just munch on it so you have a passion
너는 열정이있어서 그냥 뭉뚱그려 라.
for cooking as well now or well just I
지금뿐 아니라 잘 요리를 위해서.
never I never was a good cook before
결코 전에 나는 결코 좋은 요리사가 아니었다.
that's the thing so now that I don't
그게 내가 지금 하지 못하는 일이야.
know it's actually making me a better
실제로 그것이 나를 더 잘 만들고 있다는 것을 알아라.
cook and now I can make my own food and
요리해라. 그러면 나는 나 자신의 음식을 만들 수있다.
I know that when I'm on my own I'll be
나는 내 자신 에있을 때 나는있을거야.
okay that's probably where it's a good
좋아, 아마 그게 좋은 거야 .
experience here you go okay you don't
여기에서 경험하는 것은 괜찮습니까?
want to be eaten mr. noodle ramen
먹고 싶어. 국수라면
noodles every night hmm not every night
매일 밤 국수가 아닙니다.
now most nights yes no but I get to
지금 대부분의 밤 예 아니오. 그러나 나는 도착 한다.
prepare the staff dinners and breakfasts
직원 저녁 식사와 아침 식사 준비하기
those out loans so i get like people
사람들이 좋아 그래서 대출을 밖으로
from like others like the other staff
다른 직원들처럼
buildings are constantly coming up to me
건물들이 끊임없이 나에게 다가오고있다.
like like what's for dinner what's for
저녁 식사를 위해 무엇을 위해있는 것처럼
lunch what's for breakfast i'm like i
점심은 아침 식사를 위해 무엇이 나는 i와 같다
don't know whatever's left over like
좋아하는 일이 뭔지 모르겠다.
that that's what you guys get his
그게 니가 얻은거야.
leftovers I icon word on your twitter
남은 부분 나는 당신의 트위터 에 아이콘 단어
account Erica lalonde one I don't know
에리카 론 론데 나는 모름이다.
why I put the one I think you said okay
왜 내가 너를 그렇게 말한 것 같니?
to the wrong question be careful Erica
에리카는 조심해야한다.
galland one on Twitter I saw a picture
지저귐에 galland 하나 나는 그림을 보았다.
of the mural that you had completed yeah
네가 완성한 벽화
and actually your dad is is such a kind
실제로 네 아빠는 그런 사람이야.
of gentleman
신사
you're my provided us right now provided
너는 지금 내게 우리에게 제공되는 것이다.
us with photos which i'm not i'm not
사진이있는 우리는 내가 아니에요.
quite sure if that's a nice thing for
그게 좋은 일인가?
him to do to you or if that is there
그 사람이 너에게 할거야, 아니면 거기에 있다면
there ok ok you so you you had the
이 확인 확인을 그래서 당신했다
chance to filter these late i don't know
늦게 내가 모를 기회를 걸러 낼 기회.
what's going on here you're gonna have
여기 에 무슨 일이 일어나고 있니?
to tell us the story um that was to band
우리에게 이야기 할 음모 를 말하면서
around um right after my exam he was
내 시험 직후에 그는 주변에 있었다.
trying to get me off the two but
날 빼내려고 하지만
actually at the same time my legs were
사실 내 다리는 동시에
90 degrees in the air and he calls it
공중 에서 90도를 가리킨다.
the soup kitchen so he was driving the
수프 부엌 때문에 그가 운전하고 있었어.
boat and he goes around in a circle and
보트와 그는 서클에서 돌아 다니며
crazy and he's just going over ways and
미친 그리고 그는 단지 길을 가고있다.
you fly up in the air but he didn't
당신은 공중에서 날아 오른다. 그러나 그는하지 않았다.
didn't get a pretty epic shop yeah but
꽤 서사시적인 상점을 얻지는 않았다. 그렇지만
that's the first one all right okay um
그거 처음 괜찮아. 괜찮아.
that was Amanda country kettle a nice
아만다 (Amanda) 국가 주전자가 멋지다.
little restaurant by the hose you just
너 혼자만의 작은 식당
happen to be up on the jumbotron on the
점보트론에서 일어난다 .
bus okay yeah iceland said that they
버스 괜찮아 그래 아이슬란드 그들은
caught a nice can determining look um
좋은 음을 결정할 수 있는 걸 잡혔다.
nothing i graduate yeah that's my
아무것도 졸업하지 그래, 내거야.
graduation um very funny story she asked
그녀가 물어 보았던 매우 우스운 이야기
me if i was a nice of my auntie Tammy
내 아줌마의 멋진 Tammy라면 나.
and I said nephew exelis my phone on you
조카가 너에게 내 전화를 전했다.
at that point I know and they didn't
그 시점에서 나는 알고 있고 그들은하지 않았다.
even say my quote card like it's just
그냥 내 견적 카드라고해도 돼.
what I think when you go to graduate you
네가 졸업 할 때 내가 생각하는거야.
say something that you've always wanted
항상 원했던 걸 말하다.
to say so we got a lot of yoga Becca I
to say 그래서 우리는 많은 요가 Becca있어
don't know and I just said like focus on
모르겠다. 그리고 나는 방금에 초점을 맞췄다.
the good old times and they just said
좋은 옛날과 그들은 방금 말했다.
nothing and then said I come on and I
아무것도하고 나서 내가 와서 내가 말했다.
was like oh I am her nephew I was scared
오, 나는 그녀의 조카 였어. 무서웠다.
she's like shaking my hand and she said
그녀는 내 손을 흔들면서 그녀가 말했다.
you know Tammy you know Tammy and i'm
니가 태미 를 알면 태미를 알지.
like 'i nephew and it's just like what
'나는 조카처럼'
you just nervous waitin out i'm like
너 긴장 하고 있어.
okay and then yeah that's the finished
좋아, 그럼 끝났어.
mural ya know this is what I saw tweeted
벽화 나중에 내가 짹짹이 본 것을 알고있다.
on Twitter mm-hmm Erica lalonde one very
트위터에 mm-hmm 에리카 랄 론데 하나 아주
cool I know you've been working on that
당신이 그 일을 해왔다는 걸 알아요.
for some time yeah
몇 시간 동안 예.
two and a half months and I don't know
2 달 반 이나 모르겠다.
it's it's nice because we don't have
우리가 가지고 있지 않기 때문에 좋은거야.
anything in our school like that's the
우리 학교의 어떤 것도
first time in ten years that we actually
우리가 실제로 10 년 만에 처음으로
have art of some sort kind of bringing
어떤 종류 의 미술을 가져 오는 것
in some like I don't know some nice
어떤 사람들은 내가 좋은 걸 모르는 것 같아.
colorful joyful feelings rather than a
형형색색의 즐거운 감정보다는
white kind of right you know the
당신이 알고있는 바로 하얀 종류의
brownish school very good well well done
갈색 학교 아주 잘 잘 잘 완료
and congratulations on the graduation
축하합니다.
glad you're having a good summer yeah
당신이 좋은 여름을 보내고 있어 기쁘다 예
it's going really good how's your summer
여름은 어때요?
going it's nice to see everybody thanks
모두들 고마워요.
for joining us in the chat room category
대화방 카테고리에 우리와 합류 한
5 on freenode and you can visit our
freenode에 5 그리고 우리를 방문 할 수 있습니다
website triple w category five dot TV
웹 사이트 트리플 w 카테고리 5 도트 TV
and then also coming up in the show room
그리고 쇼 룸에 올라와.
or in the newsroom sorry Apple has been
미안하다.
as dealt an interesting in your face
너의 얼굴을 흥미롭게 다루었 다 .
blow to the benefit of samsung linux
삼성 리눅스 의 장점에 타격을 가하다.
kernel 3.5 is now available and
커널 3.5를 사용할 수 있으며
microsoft made a loss for the first time
마이크로 소프트는 처음으로 손실을 냈다.
since it joined the stock market in 1986
1986 년 주식 시장에 합류 한 이후
Wow also want to transfer data in bird
와우도 새 에서 데이터를 전송하고 싶다.
songs there's now an app for that so
노래가있는 앱이 생겼습니다.
stick around for these stories that are
이 이야기들을 위해 주위에 붙어 라.
coming up later in the show cool we've
나중에 우리가 본 멋진 쇼 에서
got your viewer questions tonight you
오늘 밤에 뷰어 질문을 받았다.
can email us live at category five dot
카테고리 5 점에서 이메일을 보내실 수 있습니다.
TV again join us in the chat room we're
TV가 다시 우리와 대화방에 참여합니다.
gonna do our best to keep up with you
너와 잘 지내기 위해 최선을 다할거야.
there nice to see Chris Reich and jot a
Chris Reich와 jot a를 만나서 반갑습니다.
gamoto Garvey who joins us quite often
가토 가비가 자주 우리와 합류한다.
through the week as well gwg a jameson
일주일 내내 제임슨도 함께
we've got tons of you an honest man nice
우리는 너의 톤이 멋지다.
to see you yeah thanks for the belated
뒤늦은 데 고마워요.
birthdays and yeah I know it's kind of
생일과 예. 나는 그것이 일종의 것임을 압니다.
hard I no one really knew about it but
열심히 나는 아무도 그것에 대해 정말로 알지 못했다.
whatever it's okay but we have a viewer
어떤 괜찮아 그러나 우리는 뷰어가
question from chas lennox from athletics
육상 경기에서 가져온 chas lennox의 질문
kitchener so Robbie install Lubuntu on
로버트가 Lubuntu를 설치하도록 부엌 관리자
my IBM thinkpad t23 it can't seem to get
내 IBM thinkpad t23 얻을 수없는 것 같습니다.
the flash working under the chronium or
chronium에서 작업 플래시 나
firefox installed and boon to restricted
파이어 폭스 설치 및 제한된 이익
extras manually installed flash as per
엑스트라는 수동으로 플래시를 수동으로 설치했습니다.
adult think the problem is the hardware
성인은 문제가 하드웨어라고 생각합니다.
since I've done this a lot flash video
내가이 일을 많이했기 때문에 플래시 비디오
we just got back on firefox on Chrome
우리 는 Chrome에서 Firefox를 다시 사용했습니다.
and it says it's missing a plug-in but
플러그인 이 누락되었다고 하지만
both work fine on my leave
둘 다 내 휴가에 잘 작동합니다.
Leonov o 3000 OBO look I'm me I'm oh
Leonov o 3000 OBO 봐 나는 나예요. 오.
yeah yeah c100 using same install
그래, 같은 설치를 사용하여 c100
process reinstalled regular and boon to
프로세스가 정기적으로 다시 설치되었습니다.
same problems do you think that the low
같은 문제는 당신 이 낮은
end video card in the laptop might be
랩톱의 엔드 비디오 카드 가
causing the flash problems hmm it can
플래시 문제 일으킬 수 있습니다.
what I'm looking at here is I just
내가 여기서보고있는 것은 내가 단지
brought up YouTube I should probably go
내가 아마 가야 YouTube를 가져
to something that I know is safe which
내가 아는 무언가에 안전하다
is category 5 TV and you'll see you know
카테고리 5 TV이고 당신은 당신이 알고있는 것을 볼 것입니다
when i when i launched a youtube video
언제 내가 YouTube 비디오를 시작했는지
for example just because this taps into
예를 들어
flash that's a good idea to test if i
플래시. 그게 내가 시험해 볼 수 있는 좋은 생각이야.
right click on and go settings you'll
마우스 오른쪽 버튼으로 클릭하여 설정 이동
notice that there's something here that
여기서 뭔가 가 있다는 것을 알아 차려라.
i've got turned off their transplant x
나는 그들의 이식 체 x에서 꺼져있어.
and it's enabled hardware acceleration
하드웨어 가속이 가능합니다.
in linux under certain situations with
리눅스의 특정 상황에서
certain drivers and graphics and things
특정 운전자와 그래픽 및 사물
that checkbox can cause some very
그 체크 박스는
strange anomalies that that will in fact
사실 이상한 이상한 예외
break your flash for for video playback
비디오 재생을 위해 플래시를 깰
so i'm not sure if that's necessarily
그래서 필자는 필연적으로 확신 할 수 없다.
what it could very well be what the
그게 뭐야.
problem is that would be the first thing
문제는 이것이 첫 번째 일이 될 것입니다.
that i would check with regard to the
나는 관련하여 확인 것이라고
modern flash also there have been some
현대 플래시 또한 일부되었습니다
known issues with I think version 11 the
알려진 문제는 버전 11이
latest version anyways since upgrading
업그레이드 이후의 최신 버전
and so you might try if if absolutely
그래서 절대적으로 시도한다면 시도 할 수도 있습니다.
everything else fails you might try
다른 모든 시도는 실패 할 수도 있습니다.
reverting to a slightly older version
조금 오래된 버전으로 되돌리기
flash from version to version tends to
버전에서 버전으로 플래시하는 경향이 있습니다.
be fairly similar these days so you know
당신이 알 수 있도록 요즘 상당히 유사
if the latest and greatest doesn't work
최신의 가장 위대한 것이 작동하지 않는 경우
for you then you can step back just a
당신을 위해 다음 단계로 돌아갈 수 있습니다.
little bit but try turning off that
조금만 그만두고
hardware acceleration in the settings
하드웨어 가속 설정
first and foremost just bring up a video
무엇보다 먼저 비디오를 가져 오십시오.
right click on a go settings and disable
이동 설정을 마우스 오른쪽 버튼으로 클릭하고 사용 중지합니다.
that that will that will hopefully bring
그게 희망적으로 가져올거야.
back for you that fixed it for me I was
다시 당신을 위해 나를 위해 그것을 해결하는 I이었다
getting black windows for flash videos
플래시 비디오를위한 검은 창문보기
and some pink you know the faces would
일부 핑크는 얼굴이 것 알고
come in and that would look all pink and
들어 오면 핑크색으로 보일거야.
blocky mm-hmm it was very strange I hope
뭉툭한 mm-hmm 그것은 매우 이상했다 나는 희망한다.
that helps for you Erika we have to take
너를 도와주는 에리카 우리가 가져야 만 해.
a quick break and and
빠른 휴식과
we're going to be back with more viewer
우리는 더 많은 뷰어로 돌아갈 것입니다.
questions after the break but stick
휴식을 취한 후에도 의문이 들다.
around and of course we're going to be
주위에 물론 우리가 될거야
looking at that app we're going to be
우리가하려고하는 그 응용 프로그램을보고
looking at tonight we're going to be
오늘 밤에 우리가 될거야.
talking about backups and I may even
백업에 대해 이야기하고 나는 심지어
have something really kind of cool to
정말 멋지다.
show you if we have time so stick around
우리가 시간이 있다면 보여줘.
we're we're going to be right back after
우리는 곧 돌아올거야.
this at eco alkalines we believe you
우리가 당신을 믿는 에코 알칼리에서.
should be able to trust your batteries
배터리 를 믿을 수 있어야합니다.
not just here but here here and here but
여기뿐 아니라 여기에 여기에 있지만
with one exception you should also be
한 가지 예외는있을 수 있습니다.
able to trust your batteries here Eco
여기에 에코를 귀하의 배터리를 신뢰할 수
alkalines of the world's first and only
세계 최초 이자 유일한 알칼리성 물질
certified carbon neutral battery
인증 된 탄소 중립 배터리
manufactured to the highest standards of
최고 수준으로 제조 된
recycling and quality without any trace
트레이스가없는 재활용 및 품질
amounts of harmful chemicals like
양 같은 유해한 화학 물질
mercury lead or cadmium eco alkalines
수은 납 또는 카드뮴 에코 알칼리
provide performance the rivals leading
경쟁사를 앞서 간다.
national alkaline battery brands at a
국가 알카라인 배터리 브랜드
comparable price find out more about the
비교 가격은 대한 자세한 내용을 보려면
Eco alkalines difference Eco alkalines
에코 알칼리의 차이 에코 알칼리
calm this is category 5 technology TV
진정해 카테고리 5 기술 TV입니다
we're online at triple w category five
우리는 온라인으로 트리플 W 카테고리 5에 있습니다.
dot TV and of course our mobile site is
도트 TV와 물론 모바일 사이트는
m dot cat five dot TV in category five
5 점 5 도트 도트 고양이 5 점
TV is also a member of the tech podcast
TV도 테크 팟 캐스트 의 멤버 입니다.
network and if it's tech it's here and
네트워크 및 기술의 경우 여기에 있습니다.
the international association of
국제 협회
internet broadcasters now I just looked
인터넷 방송사가 지금 막 보았습니다.
at the sea like the type and feed and
바다에서 유형과 사료 및
care yeah the chat room I love the
케어 예, 내가 좋아하는 대화방
comment by Maggie moto at IE college
IE 대학에서 Maggie moto의 댓글
agra modem agra boat oh uh but your
아그라 모뎀 아그라 보트 아,하지만 당신은
shirt blowing out the color filters was
셔츠가 컬러 필터를 날려 버리는
the first comment was the first thing I
첫번째 코멘트는 내가 제일 먼저했다.
said to you yeah yeah whoa look at your
워 봐 그래 당신에게 말하여
shirt I said oh this is this is me
셔츠 내가 이런 말했어이게 나야
clinging desperately on to my youth
필사적 으로 내 젊음에 집착하다.
that's take it or leave it whatever
그걸 가져 가거나 뭐든지두고 가라.
young backstage pass can read the back
젊은 무대 뒤에서 읽을 수있는 패스
perhaps if you're on backstage pass well
아마 무대 뒤에서 잘 지내고 있다면
i was thinking plaid but it pledged in
나는 격자 무늬를 생각하고 있었다. 그러나 그것은 맹세했다.
its always we're totally hip and styling
항상 우리는 완전히 엉덩이와 스타일링 이야.
today lagers is kind of like red and
오늘 lagers는 빨강과 같은 종류 다.
blue so yeah my 3d glasses it'll be whoa
파란색 그래, 내 3D 안경 그것은 워 우다있을거야
trippy like a scene from tron
트론 의 장면처럼 트리 피
so we have another question from Garvey
Garvey의 또 다른 질문이 있습니다.
Hagar me so hello guys i was watching
Hagar 나여보세요, 얘들 아.
the episode 250 250 when Robbie was
Robbie가있을 때 의 에피소드 250 250
explaining a virtual box set up to me
나에게 설정 한 가상 박스 설명
late network setup eric was trying to
늦은 네트워크 설정 에릭이 노력했다.
think of something that would need to be
있을 필요가 있는 무언가를 생각해 보라.
changed between the clones for them to
그들 사이에 복제본이 바뀌었다.
be unique I think she was trying to come
나는 그녀가 올 줄 알았어.
up with a hostname the hostname for a
호스트 명과 호스트 명
system must also be unique on a network
시스템은 네트워크에서 고유해야합니다.
virtual box itself should manage the mac
가상 박스 자체가 맥을 관리해야합니다
address so they will be unique but the
주소 가 고유하므로
hostname would remain the same and
호스트 이름은 동일 하게 유지됩니다 .
should be changed in order to run many
많은 것을 운영하기 위해 바뀌어야한다.
copies of a system on a network right
네트워크상의 시스템 사본
thanks Garvey yes oh i wish erik was
고마워 Garvey 네, 오, 제발 에릭을 원했어.
here to hear that because a couple weeks
여기 몇 주 동안
ago when Eric was here he was trying to
전에 에릭이 여기있을 때 그는
explain hostname and you're absolutely
호스트 이름을 설명 하면 절대적으로
right that's exactly what he was going
맞아, 그 사람이 가고있는 바로 그거야.
for and I was thinking MAC address he
내가 MAC 주소라고 생각하고 있었어.
wasn't explaining that he was saying s
그가 말하고 있다고 설명하지 않았다.
ID which made me think about Wi-Fi with
내가 Wi-Fi에 대해 생각하게 만든 ID
ssids and stuff so yes hostname that is
ssids 및 stuff 예 호스트 이름입니다.
your identity on the network so if you
당신의 신원 이 네트워크에 있다면
if you clone a virtual machine for
가상 시스템을 복제 한 경우
example you've got windows seven
예를 들어 윈도우 7을 가지고있다.
installed in a virtual machine and you
가상 머신에 설치하고
make a copy of that machine we I was
나는였습니다 기계 우리의 복사본을 만들
trying to grasp what Eric was saying I
에릭이 뭐라고 말했는지 알기 위해
was saying oh you need to change the
오, 너를 바꿀 필요가 있다니.
uuid of that virtual hard drive
그 가상 하드 드라이브의 uuid
obviously because otherwise it's going
분명히 그렇지 않다면 그것은 가고있다.
to think that it's two of the exact same
그것이 똑같은 두 가지 라고 생각 하는 것
hard drive and it's going to conflict
하드 드라이브가 충돌 할 것입니다.
but what he was saying is you know once
하지만 그가 한 말은 당신이 한 번 알고 있다는 것입니다.
you've booted it up you need to change
당신은 당신이 변경할 필요를 부팅 한
the hostname so that they can both run
둘 다 실행할 수 있도록 호스트 이름
on the same network otherwise you're
그렇지 않으면 같은 네트워크에 있습니다.
going to have that hostname conflict so
그 호스트 이름이 충돌 할 것입니다.
DNS won't work properly and stuff like
DNS가 제대로 물건처럼 작동하지 않습니다
that so cool thanks Garvey
그렇게 차가운 감사 Garvey
um well we have another question this is
음, 다른 질문이 있습니다.
more requests at the moment rather than
현재 요청보다
a question okay um but I'm sure it's
질문은 괜찮아요.하지만 확실 해요.
been covered before so would it be
전에 덮여 있었으니
possible to show our series of shows
우리 쇼 시리즈를 보여줄 수 있음
that goes on goes into the principles of
계속 진행되는 것은
networking I what IP addresses are in
네트워킹 IP 주소는 무엇입니까?
internal external and how to find your
내부 외부 및 귀하의 제품 을 찾는 방법
internal external IP what a network
내부 외부 IP 무엇 네트워크
gateway is how to port forward ports etc
게이트웨이는 앞으로 포트 등 을 포트 하는 방법입니다
something that is targeted towards
겨냥한 대상
beginners who wish to get into
들어가고 싶은 초보자
networking if this is not possible could
이것이 가능 하지 않다면 네트워킹 할 수있다.
you direct me to sites are targeted to
당신은 나를 목표로 하는 사이트로 안내합니다.
beginners that that's a license Robbie
초보자 는 로비 야.
thanks Robert it's a pretty vast yeah to
감사합니다 로버트 그것은 꽤 광대 한 예입니다.
say you know can you cover this in in
당신 이 이것을 안으로 들어올 수 있는지
the course of a question I and I
질문 I와 I 의 과정
understand from the beginning of your
너의 시작부터 이해 하라.
email that you and you you get that that
당신과 당신이 그 이메일을 받았다고 이메일을 보내라.
would take up a whole show practically
실질적으로 전체 쇼를 진행할 것입니다.
to get into I wouldn't mind knowing a
들어가기를.
little bit more about where you're at
당신이있는 곳에 대해 조금 더
and what what kind of things you're
네가 어떤 종류의 것들을
hoping to do networking is is something
네트워킹을 원한다는 것은 뭔가입니다.
that's great to know because the things
그 일 때문에 알고 좋아요
that you can do are just limitless I
당신이 할 수있는 것은 무한한 것입니다.
mean if you want you can if you
네가 원한다면 너는 할 수 있니?
understand networking well enough you
너를 충분히 네트워킹 이해
can be you can optimize the way that
당신은 그 방법을 최적화 할 수 있습니다.
your backups are done I've got a
당신의 백업이 완료되었습니다.
pogoplug sitting at work for example so
예 를 들어 직장에서 앉아있는 포고 플러그
that my backups can just be done to the
내 백업은
pogoplug and my server that's here
포고 플러그와 내 서버는 여기에있다.
thinks that the pogoplug is another
포고 플러그가 다른 것 같아요.
computer on our network so it's you know
우리의 네트워크에있는 컴퓨터가 그래서 당신이 알고 있어요
it's knowing how to do networking and
그것은 네트워킹을하는 방법을 알고 있고
it's it's it can be fairly basic it can
그것은 그것이 상당히 기초적 일 수 있다는 것입니다.
be quite advanced and when you
꽤 발전하고 당신이
understand things like hostname as
호스트 이름을 다음과 같이 이해하십시오.
Garvey says then you're flying but let
Garvey가 말하길 당신은 날고 있지만
me know Robert what I guess where you
내가 로버트를 알면 내가 네가 어디 있는지 짐작할거야.
it's tough that's that's such a wide why
그것은 즉 그와 같은 다양한 이유입니다 힘든
think that's like it's almost like
거의 비슷 하다고 생각해.
saying like can you can you tell us
너는 너에게 우리에게 말해 줄 수 있니?
about audio like it'sit's that that wide
it'sit 같은 약 오디오는 다양한 것을이다
of the spectrum there's so much stuff
너무 많은 것들이 스펙트럼의
that that we could get into and you know
우리가 들어갈 수 있고 너도 알다시피.
we're talking IP addresses okay so we're
우리는 우리가있어 괜찮 IP 주소를 얘기하고
looking at multiple levels of IP you
여러 수준의 IP를 보면서
you're probably using ipv4 we probably
아마도 우리는 아마도 ipv4를 사용 하고 있을 것입니다.
need to get into ipv6 the same
ipv6 에 들어가야 한다.
different versions of the IP addresses
다른 버전의 IP 주소
but yeah let's let's let's chip away at
하지만 그래, 칩을 버리자.
it let's so let me know what what
그게 뭔지 알려주지.
specifically one on what you want to
특히 하나의 당신이 원하는에
learn how to do might help me to grasp
어떻게 할 수 있는지 배우는 것은 나를 도울 수 있습니다.
what it is that you're hoping for be
네가 바라는 게 뭐야?
happy to help Thanks well we have tons
도와 드리겠습니다. 감사합니다. 우리는 톤이 있습니다.
of questions tonight so let's try get
오늘 밤에 질문을하고
through them all we have one another one
그들 모두를 통해 우리는 서로 하나가된다.
from swiss and I and so it says in lenox
스위스에서 나 그리고 그래서 레녹스에서
one of the more discouraging
더 낙담 한 것 중 하나
productivities is the process of
생산력은
installing software that doesn't come
설치되지 않은 소프트웨어 설치
via the respiratory in windows also
창문에있는 호흡기를 통해서도
talking repository sorry in windows all
미안 창문에서 말하는 모든 저장소
we have to do is start the setup etc and
우리가해야 할 일은 설정 등을 시작 하고
answer a few questions to get things
물건을 얻으려면 몇 가지 질문에 답하십시오.
started in a few seconds but to a below
몇 초 만에 시작되었지만 아래에
geeky Lennox user like me installing
나를 좋아하는 괴짜 Lennox 사용자가 설치 중입니다.
often comes as a rather lengthy and
오히려 오랜 시간이 걸리고
frustrating process hmm ya well what
절망적 인 과정 hmm 나중에 무엇
what they're saying there and and I
그들이 말하고있는 것과 거기에있는 말
thought it was interesting off the top
꼭대기에서 재미 있다고 생각 했어.
Erica read your name is Swiss and I
에리카, 네 이름은 스위스 사람이고 나는
because it's it's that's how it's
왜냐하면 그게 그게 그거야.
spelled exactly i've always said swiss
철자가 정확히 나는 항상 스위스 인 이라고 말했다.
Andy oh but isn't that's so funny how
앤디 오, 그렇지만 그렇게 재밌지는 않습니다.
two different ways that's just how i've
난했습니다 단지 방법은 두 가지 방법
read it so let us know which is the
그것을 읽으십시오. 저희에게 알려주십시오.
correct pronunciation whoever got it
누구든지 그것을 가지고 올바른 발음
right will win a prize hope it's me hope
오른쪽이 나에게 희망이되는 상을받을 것이다.
it's me i'm going to say swiss Andy just
나야, 앤디 한테는 그냥 말할거야.
because that's what I've always said
그게 내가 항상 말했던 것이기 때문이야.
using a repository and Linux is is the
저장소와 리눅스를 사용하는 것은
dreamiest way to install programs on
에 대한 프로그램을 설치하는 가장 꿈꾸는 방법
your computer I'll show you Erika what
귀하의 컴퓨터 에리카에게 무엇을 보여줄 까요?
what a repository is is capable level
저장소는 가능한 수준입니다.
just bring one I'm going to bring up
내가 가져올 게 하나 가져와 .
synaptic package manager on my computer
내 컴퓨터의 시냅스 패키지 관리자
which is basically a program that you
기본적으로 당신이
can use to install programs on your
에 프로그램을 설치하는 데 사용할 수 있습니다.
linux computer and I say this is if you
리눅스 컴퓨터와 나는 이것이 당신이
know I really I want you to I want you
내가 너를 원해.
to switch to linux okay I did but I had
리눅스로 전환 좋아 내가 그랬어하지만 난했다
issues installing you need to talk to me
나에게 얘기해야 할 설치 문제
but these bring it in let's get it on
하지만 이것들은 그것을 가져와
the show okay for the next month I have
내가 가지고있는 다음 달에 괜찮아 보여.
no internet
인터넷 없음
that's unreasonable in any time I come
그게 언제든 내가 부끄럽다.
back I have like a hundred new messages
나는 새 백개의 메시지를 가지고있다.
that I have to read because I've only
나는 단지했습니다 때문에 읽기가 있는지
been back off twice now and I've been
이제 두 번 뒤로 물러 났고
there for a week but I had a good my
1 주일간 거기에서 그러나 나는 좋았다
orientation so if I email you and it
오리엔테이션 때문에 이메일을 보내면
takes you six months to get back to me
나에게 돌아 오기까지 6 개월이 걸린다 .
I'll know why no no no I'll be back
왜 안돼, 내가 돌아올거야 .
before sit ever check out check out what
전에 체크 아웃 체크 아웃 이제까지 앉아 무엇을
a repository does here so here are the
저장소는 그래서 여기 여기 않는있다
repositories so you see that you know
리포지토리를 통해 알 수 있음을 알 수 있습니다.
i'm subscribed to the main the universe
나는 우주의 중심에 가입되어있다.
the restricted the multiverse each one
각자 제한된 다중 우주
has different kinds of software main is
다른 종류 의 소프트웨어가 있습니다.
essentially you know the the free open
본질적으로 당신 은 자유로운 열린 것을 압니다.
source stuff universe is kind of out
근원 재료 우주는 밖으로 종류입니다
there stuff restricted could be stuff
제한된 물건이 물건 일 수 있습니다.
that is considered possibly not legal in
아마도 합법적이지 않은 것으로 간주되는
certain countries and things like that
특정 국가 및 그런 것들
mp3 codecs and stuff like that that's
MP3 코덱 및 물건 그건 것을 좋아한다
its wide what you can do so with the
그 넓은 당신이 무엇을 할 수있는
repository erica what you can do is type
당신이 할 수있는 리포지토리 에리카는 타입입니다
in the name of a program last week we
지난 주 프로그램 이름으로
were talking and looking at key pass X
이야기하고 있었고, 중요한 통과 X를보고 있었다
for example and so we installed that
예를 들어 우리는
just by clicking mark for installation
설치 표시를 클릭하기 만하면됩니다.
and go so with a repository
저장소로 이동하십시오.
installations on Linux are so easy and I
리눅스에서의 설치는 매우 쉽고
think that's what's with Andy is saying
앤디가 말하는 것 같아.
on windows though you typically download
일반적으로 Windows에서 다운로드
a setup.exe file you run it it works
실행하는 setup.exe 파일이 작동합니다.
what you know is there an equivalent to
당신이 아는 것은 거기에 상응하는 것입니다.
that in Linux and usually there is and
리눅스에서는 보통 거기에
and usually that is comes in the form of
일반적으로 그것은 다음과 같은 형태로 제공됩니다.
an RPM or in our case using a debian
RPM 또는 우리의 경우에는 데비안을 사용합니다
based distribution we're going to have
우리가 가질 기반 배포
de be packages de be packages are for
패키지가되는 패키지는
the debian package manager and they they
데비안 패키지 매니저와 그들
will open on your computer if you're
네가 있으면 컴퓨터에서 열릴 거야.
using a punto they'll open in ubuntu
punto를 사용하여 그들은 우분투에서 열거야
software center and there will just be a
소프트웨어 센터에서
button that says install and it will
버튼을 누르면 설치가 시작됩니다.
actually show you a screenshot it will
실제로 당신 에게 그것을 보여주는 스크린 샷을 보여줍니다.
let you do it all that way so look for
그런 식으로 모든 것을 할 수있게하십시오.
DB packages um I think Swiss Andy was
DB 패키지 um 나는 스위스 앤디가 있었다고 생각한다.
going on to talk about yeah what pulse
무슨 맥박에 대해 얘기 하려고 계속
so I want I thought you know let's take
그래서 내가 너를 알았 으면 좋겠다고 생각해.
a look at this and see what's what's up
이것 좀 보고 무슨 일이 일어나는지 보아라.
well you said fairies an example the
당신은 요정에게 예를 들어 말했다 .
Linux version of the web pulse
웹 펄스의 리눅스 버전
application
신청
all I want to do is install it in a boon
내가하고 싶은 일은 그것을 설치하는 것이다.
to 12.4 or similar and make it start
~ 12.4 또는 그 와 비슷한 것으로 시작하여 시작합니다.
automatically at boot time but it seems
부팅시 자동으로 보이지만
to it seems I'm even two different all
나는 두 가지 다른 것 같아 보인다.
still oh don't say that no it's nothing
아직도 오, 아무 것도 아니라고 말하지 마라.
like that is it can be complex and it's
그게 복잡 할 수도 있고
a learning curve right everything is a
학습 곡선이 바로 모든 인
learning curve I had issues installing
학습 곡선 설치에 문제가 있음
it as well so yeah and and it's always
그것뿐 아니라 그래, 그리고 항상
like when you're used to windows as the
네가 창문에 익숙해있을 때처럼
example because you're used to being a
예를 들어
click on a set up dot exe you you are
당신이 설정 도트 exe 당신을 클릭하십시오
gonna think along that that way mhm
그런 식으로 생각할거야. mhm
right if you're used to doing it this
네가이 일을하는 데 익숙하다면
way if you always drive on the right
당신이 항상 오른쪽에서 운전 한다면
hand side of the road and you go
길의 손 쪽 과 당신은 간다.
somewhere where they're driving on the
운전하는 어딘가에서
left it seems weird and it seems
왼쪽이 이상하게 보입니다.
difficult and challenging so now I've
어렵고 도전적이어서 지금은
just brought up what pulse on their
방금 무슨 맥박을 가져 왔어.
website so this is what pulse org now
그래서 이것은 지금 어떤 혈압 조직입니까?
are what Paul's team is cat five dot TV
폴 팀이 고양이 5 도트 TV
/ pulse that will take you to our actual
/ 우리의 실제에 데려다 줄 맥박
team so you'll be able to participate in
팀 에 참여할 수 있습니다 .
that once you get this installed so I've
한 번 설치하면 설치가 완료됩니다.
clicked on the download of version 1.2
버전 1.2의 다운로드를 클릭
32-bit I didn't bother with the setup
32 비트 설정에 신경 쓰지 않았습니다.
script maybe I will need to let's take a
대본을 가지고 가자.
look keep yes ah yes I do need that yeah
예 예 예 예 예 예 예 예 예
see they don't really outline okay so
그들이 정말 그렇게 윤곽을 그리지 는 않아 보자.
let me explain to you what's going on
내가 무슨 일이 일어나는지 설명해 줄게 .
here see how can I understand this stuff
여기 어떻게 내가이 물건을 이해할 수 있는지 보아라.
so you know we take it for granted and
그래서 우리는 당연하다고 생각합니다.
maybe that's what it is somebody who
어쩌면 그것이 누군가의 것입니다.
designed this website is somebody who
이 웹 사이트를 디자인 한 사람은 누구입니까?
understands all this stuff and I'm sorry
이 모든 것들을 이해하고 미안하다.
that they're not giving you everything
그들이 당신에게 모든 것을주지 않고 있다고
all the information that you need
당신이 필요로하는 모든 정보
download both of those things okay
그 두 가지를 모두 다운로드하십시오.
because the setup script is actually if
설치 스크립트는 실제로 if
we look at it it's actually a script
우리 는 그것을 실제로 스크립트 라고 봅니다.
that's going to set up the permissions
그것은 권한을 설정하려고합니다.
for your kernel because the thing is is
것은 당신의 커널을 위해서 입니다.
that what pulse basically taps into your
기본적으로 어떤 펄스가
keyboard driver at the colonel colonel
대령 대령의 키보드 드라이버
level so that you're able to run what
수준을 유지하면서 무엇을 실행할 수 있는지
pulse and it's able to track your
맥박과 그것을 추적 할 수있어
keystrokes it doesn't track any of the
키 입력은
the words that you type or anything like
당신이 타이핑하거나 타이프 하는 단어
that it simply tracks the
단순히
the number of times that I click the
내가 클릭 한 횟수
letter F for example so you'll notice if
예를 들어 문자 F를 사용하면
I open that file set up permissions Sh
그 파일을 열어서 사용 권한을 설정합니다. Sh
it's just it's a Bosch script it's just
그냥 Bosch 스크립트 일뿐입니다.
goes through no problem so what I'm
아무 문제 없어. 그래서 내가 뭘하니?
gonna do or a shell script or whatever
쉘 스크립트 나 뭐든지 할거야.
there we go i'm gonna go to terminal i'm
거기에 우리는 내가 해요 단자에 갈거야있어 이동
going to show you how to do this so
이렇게 하는 법을 보여줄 거야.
we've got that set up permissions SH
우리는 그 권한 을 설정했습니다 SH
we're gonna go into the folder where I
우리는 폴더 로 들어가서
did sorry going to go into the folder
죄송합니다. 폴더에 들어갑니다.
where I downloaded it to there we are
내가 거기에 그것을 다운로드 한 곳은
and oh no that's not it CD downloads and
오, 그게 아니라 CD 다운로드 및
the there we go I'm there downloads
거기에 우리가 간다 나는 거기에있다 다운로드
plural the file name is set up dash
복수의 파일 이름 이 대시로 설정됩니다.
permissions dot SH so the first thing
사용 권한 SH가 가장 먼저 표시됩니다.
that I need to do this is what they're
내가해야 할 일은 그들이하는 일이다.
not telling you under once we understand
우리가 이해하면 우리 한테 말하지 않을거야.
what what these files are and I'm really
이 파일들은 무엇이고 나는 정말로
just showing you how to do what pulse
그냥 너에게 어떤 맥박을하는지 보여주는거야.
because it shouldn't be overly
너무 지나치지 않아야하기 때문에
complicated but what pulse is a script
복잡하지만 어떤 펄스가 스크립트인가
it's not really a program that you're
그건 네가하는 프로그램이 아니야.
installing like a windows program it's
Windows 프로그램처럼 설치하면됩니다.
just a script that's running on your
실행중인 스크립트 만
computer linux is a is a whole different
컴퓨터 리눅스는 완전히 다른 것입니다.
can of worms when it comes to that kind
그런 종류 의 웜이 될 수있다.
of stuff because you can create like
당신이 같이 만들 수 있기 때문에 물건의
basically what windows had is bat files
기본적으로 윈도우즈는 박쥐 파일
you can do entire applications based on
다음을 기반으로 전체 애플리케이션을 수행 할 수 있습니다.
the same kind of premise just creating a
동일한 종류 의 전제가
text file and that's what they've done
텍스트 파일과 그게 그들이 한 짓이야
here with what pulse so knowing that
여기에 어떤 맥박이 있니?
okay this file needs to be executive all
이 파일은 모두 임원이어야합니다.
see watch what happens if I go dot slash
내가 슬래시 점을 찍으면 무슨 일이 일어나는 지 보아라.
okay because i'm running a current
내가 현재를 운영하고 있기 때문에 좋아.
folder file I need to go dot slash and
폴더 파일 점 슬래시 및
then the file name is set up dash
파일 이름 이 대시로 설정됩니다.
permissions set up dash permissions SH
권한은 대시 권한 SH 설정
if I try to run it it says permission
내가 그것을 실행 하려고 하면 허가를 말한다.
denied the reason for that is because
그 이유 는 부인했다.
I've downloaded this in my computer to
내 컴퓨터 에이 파일을 다운로드 했습니다.
protect me linux has said this is not an
나를 보호해라.
executive ol program unless you tell it
당신이 말하지 않으면 집행 위원 프로그램
that I'm allowed to execute it so I'm
나는 그것을 실행할 수있게 허용되어 있으므로
going to do that now I'm going to do it
이제 그걸 할거야. 나는 그것을 할거야.
through the terminal so that you learn a
터미널을 통해
little bit better you can right-click on
조금 더 잘 마우스 오른쪽 버튼으로 클릭 할 수 있습니다 .
it in in nautilus or your my computer or
그것은 노틸러스 또는 내 컴퓨터에서 또는
folder browsing kind of thing in
폴더 브라우징 종류의 것
your GUI and just go properties and run
귀하의 GUI 및 속성 이동 및 실행
it as a program but what I'm going to do
그것은 프로그램으로서 그러나 내가 무엇을 하려고 할 것인가?
is going to go CH mod + X set up and and
CH mod + X가 설정 될 것입니다.
just hit tab now what I'm doing is I'm
지금 내가하고있는 일을 탭으로 치면됩니다.
adding the executive will bit to that
그에게 집행 의지 비트를 추가
program so now when I run it it's
프로그램을 실행할 때 지금 실행합니다.
actually going to go see that so that
실제로 그 때문에 볼 갈
that's being output now is in fact the
현재 출력되고 있습니다.
first line of the script it's being
스크립트의 첫 번째 줄
echoed to my terminal window so now if i
내 터미널 창에 울리므로 지금 만약 내가
run it what it's going to do is it's
그건 무엇을 할 것입니다 실행
going to allow my system to to get the
내 시스템에서
permissions now it's telling me here
지금 여기에 나와있는 권한
that it needs to be rude so what we need
우리가 필요로하는 것이 무례 할 필요가 있다는 것.
to do is go sudo dot slash set tab and
해야 할 일은 sudo 도트 슬래시 세트 탭과
that does the setup permission stop SH
그 설정 권한 정지 SH 않습니다
run that now it's going to ask you for a
이제 너를 위해 너에게 물어볼거야 .
password sudo now is going to allow this
패스워드 sudo는 이제 이것을 허용 할 것입니다.
to run as root which means basically it
기본적으로 그것을 의미하는 루트로 실행
has administrator access again to
다시 관리자 액세스 권한이 있음
protect you you from malicious software
악의적 인 소프트웨어로부터 당신을 보호하십시오.
and things Linux is is very strict so it
Linux가하는 일은 매우 엄격합니다.
will not run things as the administrator
관리자로 물건을 돌리지 않는다.
unless you force them to that's where
당신이 그 곳으로 가도록 강요하지 않으면
sudo comes in so now I'm going to hit
sudo가 들어와 지금 내가 공격 할거야.
return and I've obviously already run
돌아오고 난 분명히 이미 달렸어.
this so you'll be able to go through
이것은 그래서 당신은 통과 할 수 있습니다
that step and be able to run that no
그 단계 를 실행할 수 있어야 합니다.
problem okay so the next step is we've
문제는 좋아요. 그래서 다음 단계는 우리입니다.
got that file here and what on earth do
그 파일을 여기에서 얻었습니다.
you do with that where's the executive
당신은 그 임원이있는 곳에서
all where's the etc etc but again
모든 등 어디 다시 등하지만 다시
realizing that this is in fact strictly
이것이 사실 엄밀하게는
a script let's see what it actually
스크립트는 실제로 그것을 보자.
looks like maybe it's not a shell script
어쩌면 쉘 스크립트 가 아닌 것 같습니다.
maybe it's something else who knows
어쩌면 그것은 알고있는 다른 것일 수도 있습니다.
let's take a look CD dot slash desktop
CD 점 슬래시 데스크탑 살펴보기
there's my what pulse file I'm going to
내 펄스 파일이 내가 갈거야.
again chmod plus X what pulse because
다시 chmod 플러스 X 때문에 어떤 펄스
I'm telling it is executive all and it
나는 그것이 모두 행정부 라고 말하고 있다.
is case sensitive so capital W capital p
대문자 소문자이므로 대문자 W의 자본 p
what pulse enter okay so you can see now
어떤 맥박이 이제는 볼 수 있도록 괜찮은지 입력 하십시오.
it runs
그것은 작동한다
and you get all that kind of stuff oh
오, 그런 것들을 다 가져와. 오.
well yeah yeah I might actually fail to
잘 그래, 나는 실제로 실패 할 수도있다.
load let's try sudo dot slash what ah I
로드하자 sudo 도트 슬래시 내가 뭘 내가 아.
gotta run it as pseudo there you go now
가짜 로 실행 해봐. 지금 가라.
it's monitoring alright so now you can
지금 모니터링 할 수 있습니다.
see it's actually running on my system
실제로 내 시스템에서 실행되고 있는지 확인하십시오.
grand there it is well see that so all
거기서 굉장히 잘 보입니다.
that to get you there it's so I totally
너를 거기 에 데려다 주는 건 내가 완전히 그렇다는거야.
feel for I totally understand but know
내가 완전히 이해하지만 느끼는 것을 느낀다.
that you can see that once you get that
당신은 당신이 것을 일단 것을 볼 수
it's really just a script it's not even
그것은 실제로 는 스크립트가 아닙니다.
a program and you got to just set it as
프로그램과 당신은 단지 그것을 설정해야합니다.
executive all and run it and you got to
임원 모두 그것을 실행하고 당신이있어
run it as superuser I think you know
수퍼 유저로 실행해라. 내가 아는 것 같아.
when you're on Windows you double click
Windows에서 더블 클릭하면
on something and it can do anything to
무언가를 할 수 있고 무엇 이든 할 수 있습니다.
your system and that's ease of use but
귀하의 시스템 과 그 사용의 용이성을하지만
at the same time it's very very
동시에 아주 아주
dangerous because you can change up
네가 변하기 때문에 위험 해.
something oh they don't know how many
오, 그들은 얼마나 많은지 모릅니다.
computers come in for service that
컴퓨터가 서비스를 위해 들어온다.
somebody clicked ok on the wrong thing
누군가가 잘못된 것을 클릭했다.
like which you know you did on Twitter
당신이 트위터 에서 한 것을 알고있는 것처럼
and it happens you get so many prompts
그리고 당신은 많은 프롬프트 를 얻습니다.
day in day out ok ok ok ok leaving it
하루 종일 괜찮아. 좋아, 괜찮 니.
where's to leave me alone button and
나를 혼자두고 가야 할 곳은 어디인가?
you're just pushing them and and it does
너는 단지 그들을 밀고있다. 그리고 그것은한다.
it because it exactly I tell you what
왜냐하면 그것은 정확히 당신에게 무엇을 말하기 때문입니다.
the internet is it ok to do this is it
인터넷은이 일을하는 것이 좋습니다.
okay to do that hmm ok and you just kind
그 확인 흠하고 어쩌다 할 좋아
of at that point it's ok ok ok yeah
그 시점에서 ok ok ok 그래
leave me alone and when you're likewise
나를 혼자두고, 너도 마찬가지야.
my screen are popping up oh they're all
내 화면 이 모두들 오하다.
my files gone so you can see there that
내 파일이 사라져서
it's not it's not overly complex once
한 번 지나치게 복잡하지 않습니다.
you get it as far as the concepts behind
당신은 뒤에있는 개념들까지 그것을 얻습니다.
it but it would have been nice if on the
그것은 좋았을 것입니다.
what pulse page if they had a shown you
어떤 펄스 페이지 그들은 당신에게 표시 한 경우
how to do that a little help line yeah
어떻게 도움 라인을 조금 할
food yeah I'm in the same decision yeah
음식 그래 나는 같은 결정에있어 그래
and a typical scenarios look for a de be
일반적인 시나리오는 de be를 찾는다.
packaged there easy breezy because you
당신이 쉽게 산들 바람에 포장 했으니 까.
just double click on them just like a
그냥 두 번 클릭 하면됩니다 .
setup.exe brilliant and they also take
setup.exe brilliant 그리고 그들은 또한 가지고 간다
care of dependencies we're running
실행중인 종속성 관리
something in the terminal doesn't always
터미널의 무언가가 항상 그렇지는 않다.
a Debian package will install what that
데비안 패키지는
means is if in order to install this
이 것을 설치하려면
program and use it I have to have this
이 프로그램은 내가이 있어야 사용
program a deb package primarily a
deb 패키지를 주로 프로그램한다.
repository package as well we'll go out
저장소 패키지뿐만 아니라 우리는 밖으로 나갈거야
to the repositories download the
리포지토리에 다운로드
necessary programs and install them
필요한 프로그램을 설치하고 설치하기
for you automatically so you don't need
자동으로 필요 없으므로
to go out and find those additional
외출하고 추가로 찾는다.
things repositories are the best way to
물건 저장소가 가장 좋은 방법입니다.
do it because using a repository means
저장소를 사용 하기 때문에
as new versions of the software come out
새로운 버전의 소프트웨어가 나올 때
you're going to automatically get the
당신은 자동으로
brand new version of that software
해당 소프트웨어의 새로운 버전
unlike windows updates which typically
Windows 업데이트와 달리
only updates the operating system and
운영 체제 및
Microsoft specific products like office
사무실과 같은 Microsoft의 특정 제품
the repositories anything that you
리포지토리에는
install if i install any program
어떤 프로그램을 설치하면 설치하십시오.
whatsoever if they bring out a new
그들이 새로운 것을 내면 무엇이든지
version and release it in the
버전으로 업데이트하고
repositories I will get that update so
저장소 그래서 나는 그 업데이 트 를 얻을 것이다
all of my stuff stays up-to-date if you
내 물건들은 모두 최신 상태로 유지 됩니다.
use a Debian package or if you use
당신이 사용하는 경우 데비안 패키지를 사용하거나
scripts like this you're going to have
당신이 가지고있는 이런 스크립트들
to manually update them as you go
이동 중에 수동으로 업데이트하십시오.
because it doesn't know where you got
네가 가진 곳을 모르기 때문에
those from so stick to the repositories
그것들은 저장소에 충실합니다.
if you can cool awesome well thanks for
네가 멋진 멋진 일을 할 수 있다면
all your questions will come back with
모든 질문에 다시 올거야.
more questions after the news I think
내가 생각하는 뉴스 후 더 많은 질문
because we do have a ton of your
우리가 너의 톤을 가지고 있기 때문에
questions to to address oh yes but here
오, 그래,하지만 여기에 주소를 질문
in the top stories from the category 5
카테고리 5의 주요 기사에서
news with a UK judge has ordered Apple
영국 판사와의 소식은 애플 에게 주문했다.
to publish announcements that Samsung
삼성 전자가 발표 한 내용
did not copy the design of its iPad
iPad의 디자인을 복사하지 않았다.
according to bloomberg news agency it
블룸버그 통신사 에 따르면
says that I said the judge said one
나는 판사가 말했다.
notice should remain up on apple's
애플의 사과에 주목해야한다.
website for at least six months while
최소한 6 개월 동안 웹 사이트를
other adverts should be placed in
다른 광고는
various newspapers and magazines it
각종 신문 및 잡지
follows the US companies failed attempt
시도 실패한 미국 회사를 따른다.
to block sales out of South Korean firms
한국 기업 의 매출을 막기 위해
galaxy tab tablets at the time of the
당시 갤럭시 탭 태블릿
story was written Apple had not
이야기 는 애플이 쓴 것이 아니었다.
commented on the news that sounds like
좋아 하는 뉴스에 댓글을 달았습니다.
it would be embarrassing for a company
그것은 회사에 난처하게 될 것입니다.
that they've lived they have to make
그들이 살았던 것은 그들이 만들어야 만한다.
commercials that say no they didn't copy
복사하지 않은 광고
us that's that doesn't look too good but
우리는 그렇게 좋지는 않지만
they'll probably find some of their
그들은 아마 그들 중 일부를 찾을 거야.
apple right the point if I don't get
사과 오른쪽 내가 얻을 수없는 경우 요점
some cool guy in a leather jacket to be
가죽 자켓에있는 멋진 남자 가 될거야.
like Oh leather yeah you know he'll
오 가죽처럼 네가 그걸 알거야.
he'll make it seem suave that they took
그는 그들이 취한 수줍음처럼 보일 것입니다.
and make it very grave or hip in a way
그것을 아주 무덤이나 엉덩이로 만들라.
of that oh you know Apple better than
그 오, 당신은 애플보다 더 잘 압니다.
Microsoft Kenneth a well
마이크로 소프트 케네스 우물
linus torvalds proudly announced on
자랑스럽게 발표 된 리누스 토발즈
Saturday the immediate availability of
토요일 의 즉각적인 가용성
Lennox Colonel 3.5 the new version of
레녹스 대령 3.5의 새 버전
the colonel bringing support for some
대령이 일부 지원
new hardware plus various interesting
새로운 하드웨어 플러스 다양한 흥미로운
features such as the support for
에 대한 지원과 같은 기능
metadata base checksums in the ax t
도끼의 메타 데이터 기본 체크섬
force filesystem and improvements such
파일 시스템 및 개선을 강요한다.
as memory management fixes networking
메모리 관리가 네트워킹을 수정함에 따라
and vertel ization security and a ton
및 vertelization 보안 및 톤
more nice is it just me or is it a nice
더 좋은 것은 그냥 나 아니면 멋진가?
thing that it is not version three point
버전 3 점이 아닌 것
four point three point two six point
4 점 3 점 2 점 6 점
eight nine point three I 386 point 73.5
8 점 9 점 3 점 386 점 73.5 점
it is thank you find 5 mr. Torvalds and
5mr 을 찾아 주셔서 감사합니다 . 토발즈와
Microsoft has made the first quality
마이크로 소프트는 최초의 품질을 만들었습니다.
loss in in history after it rode off of
출발 후 역사상의 손실
the value of its online advertising
온라인 광고의 가치
business the lost came after it wrote
잃어버린 사업은 그것이 쓴 후 온다.
down the value of equality by 6.2
평등의 가치를 6.2 로 낮춘다.
billion which failed to bring the
10 억을
profits expected by Microsoft that led
Microsoft가 기대했던 이익
to a 492 million loss in the three
3 억 9 천 2 백만 손실로
months to the end of june compared with
달보다 6 월 말까지
a profit of 5.9 billion a year ago the
1 년 전에 59 억 의 이익
company has not made a loss since it
회사 는 그 이후로 손실을 내지 않았다.
joined the stock market in 1986 it took
1986 년 주식 시장에 합류했다.
over a quantum in 2007 but it struggled
2007 년에는 양적으로는 어려웠으나 어려움을 겪었습니다.
to compete with rival Google Microsoft
경쟁 업체 인 Google 과 경쟁 하기 Microsoft
is doing well in other areas despite the
다른 지역에서도 잘하고 있습니다.
client popularity if it's micra Windows
micra Windows 인 경우에 클라이언트 인기
operating system which dominated the
OS를 지배하는 운영 체제
personal computer market for many years
수년간 개인용 컴퓨터 시장
hmm you can see that and today like a
흠, 그걸 볼 수 있고 오늘은
lot of people aren't always going for
사람들의 많은 항상을 위해하지 않을 수 있습니다
Microsoft you know like I find that very
마이크로 소프트, 내가 그걸 알게 된 것 같아.
cool like we don't write these news
우리가이 뉴스를 쓰지 않는 것처럼 냉정하게
stories these these come to us and
이것들이 우리에게 오는 이야기
that's actually from BBC and the fact
그것은 실제로 BBC와 사실에서 온 것입니다.
that that they say despite the decline
그들이 쇠퇴에도 불구하고
in popularity of its Windows operating
윈도우 운영의 인기에서
system I think that that is
시스템 그게이라고 생각
is a sign right there the gathers there
거기에 징조가있다.
are so many alternatives now with Linux
리눅스 와 함께하는 많은 대안들이있다.
being kind of at the forefront and Mac
최전방 에서 일종의 맥이되고있다.
if you if you really want to switch
만약 당신이 정말로 전환 하고 싶다면
hardware too well macadam at that I find
하드웨어도 너무 멋있다.
even is for people my age like when I
내 나이처럼 사람들을위한 것입니다.
talk about what I talked about
내가 무슨 얘기를 이야기
installing linux as an operating system
리눅스를 운영체제 로 설치하기
people are like I said the little
사람들은 내가 조금 말한 것 같은데.
penguin sign and I'm like that I saw
펭귄 기호와 나는 내가 본 것과 같다.
like when I was like a five I got like
내가 5 살 때처럼 나는
five years ago or something to store and
5 년 전이나 저장하고
I'm like no it's not a store like you
너와 같은 가게가 아니야.
keep it's free like you can get it
너가 그것을 얻을 수있는 것처럼 자유롭게 해라.
online and like I just gotta learn how
온라인과 같이 나는 단지 어떻게 배워야 만하는지
to use it there you go you gotta learn
그것을 사용하려면 배워야 해.
how to unseal what pulse gallery you
어떻게 펄스 갤러리를 개봉하는 당신에게
know yeah but no like I definitely
알아, 네,하지만 확실히.
noticed that Apple like as marketing
애플이 마케팅과 같은 것을 알아 차렸다.
towards you know people my age and
내 나이와
they're now switching from Microsoft
그들은 지금 마이크로 소프트에서
Apple because it's it like we have iPods
우리가 iPod을 가지고있는 것처럼 그것은 Apple이기 때문에 Apple
like all my friends talk about is their
내 모든 친구에 대해 이야기 같은 것은 자신의
ipod iphone and that connects to their
아이팟 아이폰과 그 연결
now i pad or their you know their imac
지금 나는 패드 또는 당신이 그들의 아이맥을 안다.
or ibooks oh there's Joe you got all the
또는 ibooks 오, 거기 조있어 당신은 모든
teenagers in the world but anyways well
어쨌든 세계의 청소년들
there's now a new app that trim that
이제는 새 앱으로
transmits data at a burst of a data
데이터 버스트 (burst)에서 데이터를 전송한다.
birdsong it aims to simplify the way
새소식 은 길을 단순화하는 것을 목표 로한다.
users share images and other files
사용자가 이미지 및 기타 파일을 공유합니다.
between smartphones chirp chirp plays a
스마트 폰 사이 짹짹 짹짹
two-second long noise that sounds as if
마치 2 초 길이의 소음
it was made by a robotic Bert when heard
그것은 들었을 때 로봇 Bert에 의해 만들어졌습니다.
by other devices it triggers a download
다른 장치에서 다운로드를 시작합니다.
the software which is free to use was
자유롭게 사용할 수있는 소프트웨어는
developed by animal systems a spin-off
동물 시스템에 의해 개발 된 스핀 오프
business from the University College of
대학에서 비즈니스
London interesting I had to find out
재미있는 런던 내가 알아 내야 만했다.
more about chirp thank you for for doing
짹짹에 대해 더 많은 일을 해주셔서 감사합니다.
the news no problem tastic you can find
뉴스 아무 문제가 tastic 찾을 수 있습니다.
out more about the newsroom at newsroom
뉴스 룸의 뉴스 룸에 대해 자세히 알아 보기
category 5 TV I'll hand you this I've
카테고리 5 TV 내가 이걸 나눠 줄께.
installed chirp on this ok iPad and it's
이 ok iPad 에 설치된 짹짹이.
it's strictly available for iOS right
iOS 용으로 엄격하게 사용할 수 있습니다.
now so ipods iphones ipads i would think
이제는 ipods iphones ipads라고 생각합니다.
that as the popularity increases though
인기가 증가하면서
we'll probably see other platforms
우리는 아마 다른 플랫폼을 볼 것입니다.
you mm-hmm you think about a room full
너는 방 전체에 대해 생각해 봤어.
of people all with their iphones and
모든 사람들의 아이폰과
whatever and and chirp will just run in
그리고 짹짹이 막 달릴 거야 .
the background and no problem because
배경과 아무 문제 때문에
there is multitasking on the iDevices
iDevices에 멀티 태스킹이 있습니다.
now as you know they introduced that
이제 알다시피 그들은 그것을 소개했습니다.
because it's it's probably a good thing
왜냐하면 그것은 아마도 좋은 일 이기 때문입니다.
so now I've brought it up here you've
그래서 지금 여기 가져 왔어.
got it up there I don't know if you can
당신이 할 수 있을지 모르겠어요 거기까지있어
show the folks at home what it looks
외모를 집에서 보여줘.
like I'm kind of hard to see but just a
나는 보기가 어렵지만 단지
general kind of profile of what it's
프로필의 일반적인 종류
going to look like okay so hold that up
좋아 보이려고 그렇게 생각해라.
I'm just simply going to chirp and if
나는 단지 짹짹 울 뿐이며 만약에
you've got this installed at home feel
너는 집에 이걸 설치 했어.
free to you know turn on your your
너에게 네 차례 야.
iPhone or whatever so we're not
아이폰이든 뭐든 그래서 우리는 아니에요
connected by bluetooth we're not
블루투스에 연결되어 있습니다.
connected by Wi-Fi we're not connected
Wi-Fi로 연결되어 있습니다. 연결되지 않았습니다.
by any kind of cables or you know we
어떤 종류 의 케이블이나
don't have to bang our devices together
우리의 장치를 함께 쾅 쾅!
if you're in a room and 10 people have
방에 있고 10 명 이라도
chirp installed the theory is that it's
첩은 이론이 점이다 설치
going to everybody's going to receive
모든 사람에게가는이받을 것
that chirp adds the moment of truth
그 짹짹이 진실의 순간을 더한다.
moment approve you ready okay let's see
순간 당신이 준비를 승인 좋아, 보자
okay here we go yeah this go well did it
좋아, 여기에 우리가 간다. 잘 가라.
did you guys hear that and I picked it
너희들은 그것을 들었고 나는 그것을 골랐다.
up again if this one on tap the world
세계에서 이걸 탭하면 다시 올거야.
which receives the there you go and open
당신이 가서 거기 열어주는
in safari and so what I've actually just
사파리에서. 그래서 나는 단지 실제로 무엇을 했어.
done and you sent me the category 5 here
다 끝났어. 그리고 나에게 카테고리 5 를 보냈지.
comes got it oh look at that that's true
오, 그게 사실 인지 봐.
that's awesome that's a neat idea as it
그게 깔끔한 아이디어 야.
is just it's something you think of in
당신이 생각하는 것입니다.
your hair to be so easy it's it brings
머리가 너무 쉬워서 가져온다.
subliminal messages to a whole new level
새로운 차원의 잠재 의식 메시지
cool that is that's available for free
멋지다. 그것은 무료로 제공된다.
in the App Store for your iDevice and
iDevice 의 App Store에서
give it a try i mean rewind the video
시도해라. 비디오 되감기를 의미한다.
and install it on your your iDevice and
iDevice와 iDevice에 설치하십시오 .
push play I definitely
푸시 플레이 나는 틀림없이
if I hadn't I'd advise I'd be using that
내가하지 않았다면 나는 그걸 사용하고 있다고 충고했다.
better than a bumpin all that actually
실제로 범핑 보다 낫다.
works like so yeah these kind of weird
이런 종류의 이상한 작품처럼
new things and but doesn't work now I
새로운 일을하지만 지금 은 작동 하지 않습니다.
wonder what kind of the range is like
범위가 어떤 종류인지 궁금해.
how how well does this don't have to
어떻게 이것이 얼마나 잘 할 수있는가?
test that you'd think let's bring up
테스트 당신의이 제기 할 생각 거라고
chirp again sorry up true okay I'm gonna
짹짹 다시 미안해, 난 괜찮아.
I'm gonna like I'm gonna go way over
나는 내가 갈 길을 좋아 할거야.
here okay yeah and it picked it up it's
여기 괜 찮 아 요 그래, 그것은 그것의 그것을 집어.
still picked it it's still picked it up
아직도 그것을 집어 들었어.
well how did cool we'll have to maybe do
음, 우리가 해야 할 일은 어때?
a test and see how the ring which works
테스트하고 작동하는 링을 확인하십시오.
see any way over there it's pretty high
저쪽에 어떤 방법이든 보시면 꽤 높습니다.
frequencies all but your range is pretty
너의 범위를 제외한 모든 주파수가 예쁘다.
good like trip and then see if like
좋아하는 여행을 좋아하는 경우에 볼 수 있습니다.
someone outside can get it hold the ipad
밖에있는 누군가가 ipad를 개최 할 수 있습니다.
up over there and we'll go from that
저쪽에 가면 우리가 그걸로 갈거야.
this rosy okay as far as it end of both
이 장미 빛 이 끝나면 모두 괜찮아.
rooms Oh still got it wow there's a good
객실 오 여전히 와우 좋은 거기 있어요
you know 200 feet there cool that's true
너는 거기서 200 피트가 시원하다는 것을 안다.
get it from the the itunes store there
거기서 아이튠즈 가게에서 가져와.
you go category five technology TV is
당신은 카테고리 5 기술 TV를 간다.
brought to you tonight by quarter eee
오늘 밤에 네게 가져 왔어.
electric there the official electrical
전기 거기 공식 전기
sponsor of category 5 TV and find out
카테고리 5 TV의 후원자
more about them at quarter electric com
쿼터 일렉트릭 컴에 대한 자세한 정보
also we've got one month free trials for
또한 한 달 동안 무료 평가판을 사용할 수 있습니다.
you of netflix put a cat five dot TV /
당신 netflix의 고양이 5 도트 TV /
netflix that's going to give you all the
넷플 릭스는 모든 것을 제공 할 것입니다.
movies you can watch absolutely free for
영화 는 절대적으로 무료 로 볼 수 있습니다.
one month and once you're done it's it's
한 달 에 한 번 끝내면 끝이야.
eight bucks a month I look I actually I
한 달에 8 달러 내가 실제로 봐.
don't like I've been using it now for a
내가 지금 그것을 사용하고 있는 것을 좋아하지 마라 .
month and I just love it like whenever
달과 나는 언제나 그것을 좋아한다.
like spare time again she watched the
다시 여가처럼 그녀는
shows i want to watch like don't have to
난 필요 없어처럼보고 싶어 보여줍니다
go into finding new old shows that I
내가 낡은 쇼를 발견하게된다.
didn't know existed like sliders sliders
슬라이더 슬라이더처럼 존재하지 않았다.
and mr. d mr. no hilarious I'm watching
그리고 씨. d. 들썩 들썩하지 않다. 나는보고있다.
dead like me I just finished it I used
나처럼 죽은 나는 방금 끝냈다.
to watch that show is about like grim
그 쇼가 거의 냉랭한 것을 보는 것
reapers living a very opposite loves
리퍼 매우 반대의 사랑 생활
four types of TV shows
4 가지 TV 쇼
yeah I watched dead like me rested
예, 나는 쉬었던 것처럼 죽은자를 보았습니다.
development brought the rest of element
개발은 나머지 요소를 가져왔다.
definitely but we've already seen that
틀림없이 우리는 이미 그것을 보았습니다.
so it because we've already seen it I
그래서 우리는 이미 그것을 보았 기 때문에 나는
haven't seen it like like my friend show
내 친구 쇼처럼 보이지 않았다.
it's me first time when I'm like what is
내가 처음있을 때와 같은 때.
this I had no watch this before
이 전에 나는 이것을 보지 못했다.
hilarious and they're bringing out more
들썩 들썩 한 그리고 그들은 더 많은 것을 꺼내고있다.
there's another season coming out and a
또 다른 계절이 나오고
movie following the season yes as long
계절에 따른 영화 예
as they do a great job because the
그들은 훌륭한 일을하기 때문에
people have done that before where
사람들은 그것을 전에 어디에서 했 습니까?
they've canceled the show and then 10
그들은 쇼를 취소 한 다음 10
years later they bring out a following
몇 년 후 그들은 다음과 같은
is and it's a bomb but I'm sure they'll
그리고 그것은 폭탄이지만 나는 그들이
do really well it was a good cast anyway
어쨌든 정말 좋았어.
oh I like to buy a zoo my baby yeah we
오, 나는 동물원을 사고 싶다. 내 아기 예.
actually do have a Netflix a question oh
실제로 오 , 넷플 릭스 질문이 오
yeah we got one from Jim Bob media and
예, 우리 는 짐 밥 미디어 에서 가져 왔습니다.
it says JimBob I'm using netflix and
그것은 짐볼 말한다 나는 넷플 릭스와
I've been a member for you now as you
나는 너를 위해 지금 너를 위해 일원 이었어.
probably know Canadians of a different
아마 다른 캐나다인을 알 것이다.
selection to choose from than the US yes
미국 보다 선택할 수있는 예
I realized that as well I came across a
나는 또한 내가 우연히 만난 것을 깨달았다 .
site that allows members in Canada the
캐나다의 회원들이
same selections as a US on netflix using
netflix에서 미국과 동일한 선택 사용
their server they say it's not a VPN and
그들의 서버 는 VPN 이 아니라고 말합니다.
supposedly fast i tried it for a free
아마 빨리 나는 그것을 무료로 시도했다.
7-day trial and it wasn't and i was
7 일간의 재판이 있었고 그렇지 않았습니다.
impressed with the speed but i have
속도에 감동 하지만 나는 가지고있다.
fiber cable as well so I was um I was
광케이블도 그렇고 내가 음 ..
able to receive Netflix us on my smart
내 스마트하게 넷플릭스 를받을 수있다.
TV upgrade box and a lot more services
TV 업그레이드 상자 및 더 많은 서비스
on my WD live box but I like to get your
하지만 내 WD 라이브 상자 나는 당신을 얻을 좋아
opinion on the service yeah the tricky
서비스 예에 대한 의견은 까다 롭습니다.
thing with that kind of stuff is that it
그런 종류의 물건을 가진 것은 그것이
is kind of a gray area as far as legal
법적으로 가능한 한 회색 영역입니다.
wise i'm not sure why netflix canada has
현명한 나는 왜 netflix 캐나다가 있는지 모르겠습니다.
different programming the netflix us but
다른 프로그래밍 netflix 우리지만
i would expect that it has to do with
나는 그것과 관련 있다고 기대할 것이다.
copyright laws or something of that sort
저작권법 또는 그런 종류의 무언가
so with with these kind of services as
그래서 이런 종류 의 서비스로
you say they say they're not a VPN but
당신은 그들이 VPN이 아니라고 말합니다.
usually it's done through a VPN kind of
일반적으로 VPN 유형을 통해 이루어집니다.
tunneling or something like that with
터널링 또는 이와 비슷한 것
those types of services typically you
이러한 유형의 서비스는 일반적으로
know if your travel
너의 여행을 안다.
then it's a different kind of thing
그러면 그것은 다른 종류의 것입니다.
because you're you own the service let's
너는 너 자신 이니까.
say you own it in the United States and
당신은 미국에서 자신의 말과
you travel to Canada and you you want to
당신은 캐나다로 여행하고 싶습니다.
still be able to watch your shows that's
아직도 당신의 쇼를 볼 수 있습니다
one thing but if you live in Canada you
한 가지하지만 당신은 캐나다 당신에 거주하는 경우
don't have a United States address do
미국 주소가 없다.
you have the legal right to watch a
당신은 법적인 권리를 가지고 있습니다.
service that is legally only available
법적으로 유효한 서비스
in the United States so it would I would
미국에서 그렇게하면
think that would specifically be a
그게 구체적으로
question probably for Netflix mm-hmm
Netflix mm-hmm에 대한 질문
which you can contact them by email not
이메일로 연락 할 수 없습니다.
by email by phone off of their website
웹 사이트에서 전화로 이메일로
and again it's right on camp 5 TV /
그리고 다시 캠프 에서 맞습니다. 5 TV /
Netflix you'd probably ask them if
Netflix 당신은 아마 그들에게 물어볼 것입니다.
there's a legal issue there but again
거기에 법적 문제가 있지만 다시
it's a gray area because the the modern
그것은 회색 영역입니다 왜냐하면 현대
web has progressed faster than the the
웹은
copyrights and the way that things are
저작권 및 일을하는 방법
copyrighted in today's modern internet
오늘의 현대 인터넷에 저작권이있다.
so I think that has something to do with
그래서 나는 그것이 무언가와 관련이 있다고 생각합니다.
it so yeah for reason why it's different
왜 그렇게 다른지 이유 때문에 그렇습니다.
know like i know the u.s. netflix has
내가 netflix 우리가 알고있는 것처럼 알아.
let more selections yeah but a lot of
더 많은 선택권을 가지지 만,
the the companies that are creating this
이것을 만드는 회사
content okay our American yes so are
내용 괜찮아요 미국인 그래, 그렇다
they saying no we won't allow it to be
그들은 우리가 그것을 허용하지 않을 것이라고 말합니다 .
distributed in Canada and so then if
캐나다에 분산 되어 있다면
you're tapping into a service that
너는 그 서비스를 이용하고있다.
allows you access to that you're you're
당신이 당신이
maybe not necessarily breaking the law
어쩌면 반드시 법을 어 기지 않는 것은 아닙니다.
but it's possible that the service that
하지만 그 서비스 가
is providing that may be on the verge or
직전 일 수도 있고 제공 할 수도 있습니다 .
kind of on that line of maybe they're
어쩌면 그런 종류의
stepping in somewhere that is as little
어딘가에서 조금씩 나아가는
bit past the grey area so it's hard to
회색 영역을 지나쳐 조금 어려워지기 쉽습니다.
say but I mean those services can work
말하지만 서비스가 작동한다는 의미입니다.
absolutely if you want my technical
내 기술을 원한다면 절대적으로
opinion they can certainly work I think
그들은 분명히 일할 수 있다고 생각합니다.
they're a cool idea but I think it would
그들은 멋진 아이디어지만 나는 그것이
be really great if the world wide web
월드 와이드 웹이라면 정말 대단하다.
was a world wide web but it's kind of
월드 와이드 웹했지만 그것은 종류의
like you know your cable TV is different
너는 너의 케이블 TV가 다르다는 걸 알지?
in the States versus canada to write so
캐나다 대 캐나다는 이렇게 쓰고있다.
mm-hmm take it for what it is I got
mm-hmm 그것이 무엇인지에 관해 가지고 가라.
three channels in my room awesome and no
나의 방의 3 개의 채널은 굉장하고 아니오
internet so you can't install in that
인터넷에 설치할 수 없으므로
place Oak tragic but that was the thing
오크 비극을 놓아 뒀지 만 그게 문제 였어.
like I didn't bring a single movie yeah
내가 단 하나의 영화를 가져 오지 않았던 것처럼
I did I thought when I get up there I
나는 내가 거기에 도착했을 때 나는 생각했다.
tap into their internet because like
같이 인터넷에 접속하기.
that's usually what you do tapped into
그건 보통 네가 할 일이야.
the
그만큼
internet opened up google sorry reload
인터넷은 Google 미안 재충전을 열었습니다.
page okay net fence about going netflix
넷플 릭스에 대해 괜찮은 그물 펜스 페이지
sorry reload page okay no Wi-Fi signals
죄송 페이지를 다시로드하십시오. Wi-Fi 신호가 없습니다.
nearby earn like they say they have it
인근의 수입은 그들이 가지고 있다고 말한 것과 같습니다.
but it doesn't work people brought their
하지만 사람들이 자기들을 데려온 것은 효과가 없습니다.
xboxes people are trying to get on the
xboxes 사람들은 에 도착 하려고 합니다.
live and like we're all try to game and
우리 모두가 게임을하려고하며 살아가는 것처럼
stuff but no and I don't clean out
물건을 제외하고 나는 깨끗하게하지 않는다.
houses good guy I prep food that's for
좋은 녀석들. 나는 음식을 준비한다.
housekeeping and I feel bad for them but
가사와 나는 그들을 위해 나쁘다고 느낀다. 그러나
yeah but um no so I came back and
그래, 음, 아니 , 돌아 왔어.
grabbed like a hundred different movies
100 개의 다른 영화처럼 움켜 쥐었다.
that I could possibly find but it's hard
내가 찾을 수는 있지만 힘들다.
when oh I had netflix i just had
오, 내가 넷플 릭스를 가지고 있었을 때 나는 단지 가지고 있었다.
everything there is a pre-planned wrote
모든 것이 미리 계획된 쓴다.
everything down I'm gonna watch so yeah
아래로 모든 것 나는 그렇게 볼거야.
that's I could send you some VHS I think
그게 내가 생각하기에 너에게 몇 가지 VHS를 보낼 수있어.
I met my mic is my note did it you good
나는 내 음을 만났어. 너 잘 했어.
is it better now okay can you hear me
그것이 지금은 더 좋아 당신이 나를들을 수있다
now America only Erica do you hear me
지금은 미국 만 에리카가 내 말 듣고있어?
now it's a load old food and I got asked
지금 그것은 오래되었던 음식을 로드 한다. 그리고 나는 묻게되었다
like a million times iphone smartphone
백만 번 아이폰 스마트 폰 처럼
no teen I that's what's up yeah we're
아니 십대 나는 그게 뭔지 우리가있어
Garvey says where are the cat five bars
Garvey 가 고양이 다섯 바가 어디에 있는지 말합니다.
have we got three bars or four bars
우리는 3 개의 막대 또는 4 개의 막대를 가지고 있는가?
signals good signals good you can see
신호 좋은 신호를 볼 수 있습니다.
that yeah oh yeah a signal red very good
그 예, 오, 예, 신호 빨간색 아주 좋아.
I'm not very good with out of my first
나는 처음부터 너무 잘 하지 않는다.
nose what are you doing wit now you've
코 지금 뭐하고 있니?
got a laptop computer mm-hmm we've
랩톱 컴퓨터가 있어요.
talked it before what are you doing for
너를 위해 무엇을하기 전에 말 했니?
your backups and be honest with me if
백업 날 경우 정직
you're not doing anything tonight it
너 오늘 밤 아무것도 안하고있어.
actually I have a little hard drive and
실제로 나는 작은 하드 드라이브가 있고
I've just been kind of putting it on
난 그냥 그것을두고 가지 봤는데
there but no you put it on there I've
거기에 그걸 넣어 놨어.
just been copying and saving my files
방금 내 파일을 복사하고 저장하고있다.
good
좋은
mostly just my music my photos a lot of
주로 내 음악 내 사진을 많이
the stuff that I've been doing on my
나는에 해왔 던 물건 내
computer I've managed to actually
컴퓨터 를 실제로 관리 했습니다.
restore the last four years of high
지난 4 년을 최고로 회복시키다
school because I lost a lot of my files
학교에서 내 파일을 많이 잃어 버렸어.
and stuff that I did when my old laptop
내 오래된 노트북을 할 때 내가했던 것들
kind of fried on me but now I have like
나는 종류의 튀김 그러나 지금 나는 품는다
from grade 9 to grade 12 I can look at
9 학년에서 12 학년으로 볼 수 있습니다.
the projects I've done and I'm able to
내가 해낸 프로젝트들.
just like a little mini one but other
다른 미니 미니 처럼
than that I haven't really had the time
보다 정말 시간이 없었어요
to look into anything else as well as
다른 것뿐만 아니라
backing up I had I mean I see people
후원하기 나는 사람들을 보았다는 것을 의미했다.
coming in all the time with failed hard
항상 힘들게 지내다
drives and things like that and and a
드라이브와 그런 것들, 그리고
particular gentleman came in this week
특별한 신사가 이번 주에 왔어.
who had purchased an external hard drive
누가 외장 하드 드라이브를 구입 했습니까?
one of those mini external hard drives
미니 외장형 하드 드라이브 중 하나
and had in fact been clearing the files
실제로 파일을 지우고있었습니다.
off of his laptop on to that hard drive
그 하드 드라이브 에 자신의 노트북의 오프
so it's only mine doesn't do that though
그래서 그것은 내 것이지만 그렇게하지 않습니다.
so you're running a particular program
특정 프로그램을 실행하고 있습니다.
that actually runs a real backup we've
실제로 우리가 실제로 백업을 실행합니다.
looked at some here on the show like The
The와 같은 쇼에서 여기를 보았습니다.
click free device for example which are
예를 들어 무료 장치를 클릭하십시오.
fantastic for for that but if you buy
환상적이지만 구매하는 경우
typically when you buy a piece of
일반적으로
hardware like that an external hard
그런 하드웨어는 외부 하드
drive it's it is just a hard drive you
드라이브 그것은 단지 하드 드라이브입니다.
plug it in and just comes up and it's
플러그를 꽂아주세요.
good its own Drive letter and you're
좋은 자체 드라이브 문자와 당신이있어.
good to go so people and I see it all
사람들과 내가 모두 그것을 볼 수 있도록 좋은
the time take their photos and drag it
시간은 자신의 사진을 가지고 그것을 드래그
onto that and move them so what happens
그 위에 움직여서 어떻게 움직일 지
then and unfortunately what happened to
그 다음에 불행히도 무슨 일이 일어 났습니까?
this this guy is that I'm we live in a
이 녀석은 내가 우리가 살고있는거야.
digital age you've got digital cameras i
디지털 시대 당신은 디지털 카메라를 가지고있어.
use digital video cameras all of our
우리 모두의 디지털 비디오 카메라를 사용하십시오.
family videos my kids the birthday
가족 동영상 내 아이들 생일
parties that they've had and everything
그들이 가진 파티 와 모든 것
are all stored on like these kind of
이런 종류의
deals yeah you know so then I import
네가 알기에 거래를하다가 가져온다.
them what do I do with them do I put
내가 그들과 함께해야합니까 무엇이 그들에게 내가 배치해야합니까
them on my computer and then move them
내 컴퓨터에서 그들을 누른 다음 그들을 이동
onto this Drive put him on both
이 드라이브에
unfortunately this guy had been moving
불행하게도이 사람은 움직이고 있었다.
them off of his laptop thinking well I
나는 생각하는 그의 노트북에서 벗어났다.
need that space to import more so I'm
그 공간이 더 필요해.
moving it onto this external hard drive
이 외장 하드 드라이브로 옮기기
and then the hard drive crashed and of
그런 다음 하드 드라이브가 고장났다.
course that means all of his digital
물론 그의 모든 디지털
photos of him and his family and and you
그와 그의 가족의 사진과 당신
know possibly loved ones that
아마도 사랑하는 사람들을 알고
have have moved on and that you know
계속 전진 해왔다.
those photos are priceless you can't
그 사진들은 귀중한 것입니다.
recreate that stuff and that was the one
그 물건을 다시하고는 하나
place that it once was on this external
한때이 외부에 있었던 장소
hard drive so if you get one of these
하드 드라이브 그래서 만약 당신이 하나를 얻을
hard drive the important thing to
하드 드라이브가 중요한 것
understand is that a backup is not
이해는 백업이 아니라는 것입니다.
moving your files onto another medium
다른 매체로 파일 이동하기
simply just making a second copy having
단순히 두 번째 사본을 만들기 만하면됩니다.
redundancy always having multiple copies
항상 여러 복사본이있는 중복성
this guy said well can I not just get a
이 녀석은 잘 됐어.
particular external hard drive that like
특정 외장형 하드 드라이브
isn't there a brand that doesn't fail
실패하지 않는 브랜드가없는
like do they all like why are they all
모두 왜 그런가?
junk no its you never know like that's
그건 같은 쓰레기는 모르는 더는 당신이 결코
the thing my laptop you never know when
내 노트북 ​​언제 네가 알 수없는 건
is just gonna stop working one day one
언젠가는 하루 일하는 것을 멈추게 될 것입니다.
of the guys at work is famous line is
직장에서 남자들의 유명한 라인은
it's not if it's when yeah it's it's
그것이 맞다면 그것은 그렇지 않다.
going to happen your hard drive is going
하드 드라이브가 진행될 것입니다.
to crash if your hard drive crashes
하드 드라이브가 고장난 경우 충돌이 발생합니다.
tonight it's not much we did we did not
오늘 밤 은별로하지 않았어.
try to you know spook anybody oh but it
당신은 이런 사람을 놀라게 알고하려고하지만
just it happened I do want to spook
그냥 일어난 일이야. 나는 놀래고 싶다.
people though because I it's going to
내가 그렇게하기 때문에 사람들.
happen when is it going to happen you
너 언제 일어날 거야?
have no idea so this guy's moved all of
이 녀석이
his files over and then hard drive
하드 드라이브를 통한 파일
crashes and he's lost everything all of
추락하고 그는 모든 것을 잃어 버렸어.
his digital videos all of his digital
그의 디지털 비디오는 모두 자신의 디지털
pictures music who cares i mean you can
당신이 할 수있는 것을 걱정하는 그림 음악
get the music again but all of the
다시 음악을 얻을 수 있지만, 모든
priceless stuff that you can't get again
다시 얻을 수없는 귀중한 물건
this is technically gone like I don't
내가하지처럼이 기술적으로 사라
like all my little funky little projects
내 모든 작은 펑키 작은 프로젝트처럼
I did on my last laptop or just like
나는 마지막 랩톱에서 또는 그랬다.
scripts ideas anything you want to type
입력 할 내용을 스크립트로 작성
down like I lost most of it i could only
나는 그것의 대부분을 잃어 버렸던 것처럼 나는 단지 할 수 있었다.
like literally get i only got probably
글자 그대로 나는 단지 아마 얻는다.
two gigs out of 60 of what i had filled
내가 채운 60 개 중 2 개의 공연
on there right at the time which was a
그 당시에 는
lot but not anymore 47 47 in the
더 이상은 아니지만 47 47
challenge says that a raid one is always
도전은 습격 이 항상있다 라고 말합니다.
backed up and so that's another mindset
백업 된 그래서 또 다른 사고 방식이야.
math man that is sword of let me give
나에게 줄 칼의 수학 남자
you a scenario raid one is basically
너는 기본적으로 시나리오를 습격했다.
when you have two hard drives or more
두 개 이상의 하드 드라이브가있는 경우
and they're always duplicates of each
그리고 그들은 항상 각각의 복제본입니다.
other so if i save a file i now have it
다른 그래서 만약 내가 파일을 저장하면 지금 가지고있다.
on two hard drives so if one hard drive
두 개의 하드 드라이브에 하나의 하드 드라이브
crashes I
충돌 나는
another hard drive is that a backup no
다른 하드 드라이브는 백업이 없습니다.
that's the same its redundancy which is
그것은 동일한 중복성 입니다.
a good thing but what happens if you
좋은 일이지만, 만약 당신이
have a fire what happens in a case like
다음과 같은 경우에 일어날 일이있다.
that or what happens if you get hit by a
그 또는 무슨 일이 생기면
power surge I've had that happen you
파워 서지 내가 너 한테 일어난 일 이야.
know that we had some times here where
우리가 여기서 몇 시간을 보냈던 곳을 알아라.
we had some power surges awesome
우리는 몇 가지 파워 써지가 굉장했다.
hardware and it's not selective as to
하드웨어 및 선택 사항이 아닙니다.
which of your two hard drives go good
두 하드 드라이브 중 어느 것이 좋을까요?
guy mentioning in the in the chat room
채팅방 에서 언급 한 사람
what about robbers we had somebody break
우리가 가진 강도에 대해서는 어쩌고?
into the studio and steal a whole bunch
스튜디오에 넣고 한꺼번에 훔치다.
of stuff what if our raid one set was
우리가 습격 한 세트가
part of that it's not technically a
그 중 일부는 기술적으로
backup it's a fail-safe as far as in
백업은 페일 세이프까지
business a raid one is great because if
사업은 대단한 일이기 때문에
a hard drive fails you're still up and
하드 드라이브가 고장 났다.
running your server doesn't stop working
서버를 실행해도 작동이 멈추지 않습니다.
it keeps going off the other hard drive
다른 하드 드라이브에서 계속 이동합니다.
you replace that hard drive and it
당신은 그 하드 드라이브 를 대체 하고 그것을
rebuilds the set but it's not something
세트를 재구성하지만 무언가가 아닙니다.
that you're taking off site it's not
너는 그 자리에서 벗어나고있다.
something that is an actual backup a
뭔가 실제 백업입니다
backup is not is is is redundancy
백업이 중복되지 않습니다.
obviously but it's redundancy that is
분명하지만은 중복입니다
separate from your existing system if
기존 시스템 과 분리 된 경우
it's an external hard drive it means
그것은 외부 하드 드라이브의 의미입니다.
you're unplugging it and putting it away
당신은 그것을 뽑고 그것을 버리고 있습니다.
putting in a safety deposit box getting
안전 금고에 넣어 점점
it somewhere else state is saving it at
다른 곳에서 그것을 저장하고있는 다른 곳
a family member's house but definitely
가족의 집이지만 분명히
getting it unplugged because I think of
내가 생각하기 때문에 플러그를 뽑는 것 .
power surges and if it's plugged into
전력 과다 그것은에 연결 않다면
USB in the same server that gets fried
튀겨지는 동일한 서버의 USB
or computer if your computer gets fried
또는 컴퓨터가 튀겨지면 컴퓨터
in a power surge and then your hard
힘의 서지와 너의 하드
drive is attached to it guess what so
드라이브가 그것에 붙어 있는 무엇이 그렇게 추측한다.
and that's also another thing like you
그리고 그것은 당신 같은 또 다른 것입니다.
could have your hard drive attached to
하드 드라이브를 연결할 수 있습니다.
your laptop but it's good to have that
네 랩탑 컴퓨터를 가지고 있어도 좋지만
may be hard drive put away in an old
하드 드라이브 가 오래 되었을 수도 있습니다.
laptop box or something of just all of
노트북 박스 또는
your older pitchers like buy a hard
너의 나이가 많은 투수는 열심히 산다.
drive to like once it's filled up well
일단 그것이 잘 채워지면 좋아하게된다.
if it's a terabyte or something yeah it
테라 바이트이거나 뭔가 있다면
takes a while to the wash your back up
당신의 백업을 씻으려면 시간이 걸립니다.
not everything is yeah yeah like it's
모든게 네가 좋아하는 건 아니야.
just a key like you could have like
너처럼 키가 좋아.
years I don't know like the first years
년 나는 첫번째 년을 좋아하지 않는다.
of your life too I like the middle part
네 인생의 중간 부분도 좋아해.
just all on one is my first tenure first
단지 하나의 모든 것이 나의 첫번째 재임 기간이다.
I like the idea of a safety deposit box
나는 안전 금고에 대한 아이디어 를 좋아한다.
or if you have an office at work and
또는 직장에 사무실이 있고
you've got a locking drawer or something
잠겨있는 서랍 같은 걸 가지고있어.
stick it
그것을 붙이다
their cousin get it off site cuz now
그들의 사촌은 이제 사이트에서 사촌 떨어져
that you know photo albums are slowly
사진 앨범이 천천히 있다는 것을 알고 있다고
disappearing that you know I still have
내가 아직도 알고 있다는 사실이 사라지고 있다.
them but in the next generations like
하지만 다음 세대처럼
they're not going to have as many photo
그들은 많은 사진을 가지지 않을거야.
albums unless you're actually going to a
당신이하지 않는 한 앨범은 실제로 갈거야
walmart to get it printed to get the
월마트가 그것을 얻기 위해 인쇄를 얻으려고
photos printed like like a safety
사진은 안전처럼 인쇄되었습니다.
deposit box for one of those is like
그 중 하나를위한 예금 상자는 같다.
it's it's definitely necessary if you
그것은 분명히 필요합니다.
want to keep those memories at least if
적어도 그 추억을 지키고 싶다면
you're anything happens to your computer
컴퓨터에 아무 일도 없다.
room flood anything like you never know
너가 결코 모르는 것 같이 방 홍수 아무것도.
mm-hmm so what do you do at home with
mm-hmm 그래서 집에서 무엇을합니까?
regards to your backups and are you
당신의 백업을 존중하고 당신 은
keeping a redundant backup that's the
중복 백업을 유지합니다.
question tonight I want to know and and
질문 내가 알고 싶은 오늘 밤
I want you to have the confidence that
나는 너에게 자신감 을 가져 주기 바란다.
you have copies of your stuff in two
너는 너의 물건을 2 장 가지고있다.
places at once a minimum two places
한 번에 최소 두 곳을 배치한다.
flash drives you know the USB drives are
플래시 드라이브는 USB 드라이브가
very unreliable those kind of things
그런 종류의 일은 매우 신뢰할 수 없다.
they are good for transferring stuff
그들은 물건을 옮기는 데 좋다.
back and forth from your computer to
컴퓨터에서 앞뒤로
your laptop and I've never even used it
당신의 노트북과 나는 그것을 사용한 적이 없다.
as a backup work you can't don't ever
백업 작업으로 당신은 이제까지 할 수 없습니다.
use it as a backup don't you don't store
백업으로 사용 하지 마십시오. 저장하지 마세요.
anything on those things because they
그 일 때문에 뭐든지
fail and they fail hard and you can't
실패하고 그들은 열심히 실패하고 당신 은 할 수 없다.
get your data off of them if they do in
그들이하는 경우 귀하의 데이터를 얻을
most cases so and the nurse you know
대부분의 경우와 당신이 아는 간호사
I've seen it's been plugged into the
나는 그것이에 연결되어 봤어요
computer and the cleaning person came
컴퓨터와 청소부가왔다.
through like this and snapped the USB
이것을 통해 USB를 찍었습니다.
right off and it you know stuff happens
바로 꺼내서 물건을 알아.
right so my guys I measure at school
맞아, 내 녀석들은 내가 학교에서 측정 해.
like you would even plug them in and
당신도 그걸 끼워 넣는 것처럼
then a little screen would pop up saying
그러면 작은 화면이 나타납니다.
they have to do a virus check because
그들은 바이러스 검사를해야합니다.
people were putting viruses in this
사람들이이 바이러스에 바이러스를 넣고 있었다.
school right and then they were just
학교 바로 그때 그들은 단지
people to steal I would never do a thing
사람들 이 훔칠 일을 결코하지 않을 것입니다.
like that let's plug it a virus is a
바이러스를 꽂으면 바이러스가
good school system shot is using unraid
좋은 학교 시스템 총을 unraid 사용하고 있습니다.
but no external backup no place to store
외부 백업없이 저장할 위치가 없습니다.
it I would suggest now unraid is is a
나는 지금 unraid를 제안 할 것이다.
redundant solution you've got single
단일화 된 중복 솔루션
drive failure protection and if more
드라이브 장애 보호 및 더 많은 경우
than one drive fails you only lose the
하나의 드라이브가 실패하는 것보다
data on one hard drive so that's pretty
하나의 하드 드라이브에있는 데이터가 예쁘다.
decent yeah that's what I use is my
괜찮은 예, 내가 사용하는 것은 내 것입니다.
system here but then I've also taken it
시스템은 여기에 있지만, 나는 또한 그것을 취했다.
one step further and I've thrown a
한 걸음 더 나아가서 나는
pogoplug across town and put it
마을을 가로 지르는 포고 플러그
somewhere
어딘가에
and I back up my stuff over the internet
인터넷을 통해 내 물건 을 백업합니다.
on a regular basis so I always have a
정기적으로 나는 항상
redundant copy if that's not an option
중복 복사 가 옵션 이 아닌 경우
for you and usually you can you know you
당신을 위해 그리고 보통 당신은 당신을 알 수 있습니다.
might be able to find a friend or
친구를 찾을 수 있거나
something that that you could swap you
네가 너를 바꿀 수있는 어떤 것
know install a pogoplug at their place
그들의 장소에 포고 플러그를 설치하는 것을 아십시오.
and offer to let them back up their
그 (것)들이 그 (것)들을 위로 보도록 제안하십시오
stuff to your server for example just
귀하의 서버에 물건을 예를 들어 그냥
encrypt it on his way over and you're
을 통해 자신의 길을 암호화하고 당신이있어
good to go there are ways to get your
거기에 가기에 좋은 방법을 얻을 수 있습니다.
stuff in other places but John I would
다른 곳의 물건 이지만 존
suggest that you get into a scenario if
이 시나리오의 경우에 들어갈 것을 제안
you're using on raid you're obviously
네가 분명히하는 습격에 너는 사용하고있어.
you've got a fair bit of data get
당신은 상당한 양의 데이터를 얻었습니다.
yourself even if it needs to be just a
비록 그것이 단지
single hard drive you can buy 3 terabyte
당신 이 3 테라 바이트를 살 수 있는 단일 하드 드라이브
hard drives now external drives for you
하드 드라이브는 이제 외부 드라이브로 사용할 수 있습니다.
know the prices going down mm it was
가격은 mm 추락 알고는 있었다
very very high there for a while but
아주 아주 높은 곳이지만
things are getting better since you know
네가 알기 때문에 상황이 나아 지고 있다.
since supply and demand is kind of
공급과 수요가 종류이기 때문에
shifting so but get into a scenario
변화하지만 시나리오에 들어가기.
where you've got redundancy beyond just
그냥 넘어 중복을 가지고 어디에
the system itself make sure you've got
시스템 자체는 당신이 가지고 있는지 확인합니다.
something that you can take away yeah
당신이 데려 갈 수있는 무언가 그래
for sure one viewer in the chatroom I
대화방의 I에서 반드시 하나 개의 뷰어
didn't catch the name was mentioning
이름을 붙잡지 않았다는 언급
about using the cloud yes I was looking
구름을 사용하는 것에 대해 예를 찾고있었습니다.
at that as well and and that's fine too
그걸로도. 그리고 그건 괜찮아.
but again now we used it before and what
그러나 다시 지금 우리는 전에 그것을 사용했고 무엇을
the cloud is I mean the cloud is just a
구름은 구름이 단지
pseudo term defining network storage on
네트워크 저장소를 정의하는 의사 용어
the Internet it's not something new it's
인터넷은 새로운 것이 아닙니다.
been around since the 70s and they just
70 년대 이후로 주변에 있었고 그들은 단지
rebranded it to make it sound cool
재 상표 그것이 멋진 사운드를 만들려면
really it's legit so the the cloud or
정말 합법적 인 것이므로 클라우드 나
computers out there on the internet
인터넷에있는 컴퓨터
where is your data being stored that's
귀하의 데이터는 어디에 저장되어 있습니까?
kind of the question is if if I is a
질문의 종류는 만약 내가
Canadian citizen protected under the
캐나다 시민권 보호 아래
Canadian Privacy Act am storing my stuff
캐나다 사생활 보호법
in the cloud down in the United States
미국 의 구름 속에
that is not protected by the Canadian
캐나다에 의해 보호받지 못하는
Privacy Act who has access to my data
내 데이터에 액세스 할 수있는 개인 정보 보호법
can the government read my stuff and
정부가 내 물건을 읽을 수 있을까?
look at my pictures I don't know why
왜 내 사진을 봐야 할지 모르겠다.
they would but I'm just saying there are
그들은 말했을뿐입니다.
privacy concerns there do you know where
사생활 보호에 대한 우려는
your stuff is and also is it again is it
너의 물건도 있고 또 다시 그게니?
redundant again people will move their
여분의 사람들 이 다시 이동합니다.
stuff to the cloud and then what
구름에 물건을 넣고 무엇을
as if the cloud goes down what happens
마치 구름이 무너지는 것처럼
if something weird happens and for some
이상한 일이 생기고 어떤 일로 인해
reason you lose access to your account
계정에 액세스 할 수없는 이유
what if somebody hacks your account and
누군가 귀하의 계정을 해킹 하고
deletes all the stuff and it's gone what
모든 것들을 삭제하고 사라 졌어요.
if people get ahold of many cloud
사람들이 많은 구름을 앓다 면
accounts like yeah hackers are at work
예 해커가 일하고있는 계정
who knows but then you're in a that's
누가 알 겠어? 하지만 니가 그거에 빠졌어.
again that's great for redundancy if
다시 잉여에 유용합니다.
it's a secondary copy absolutely don't
그것은 절대적으로 보조 사본입니다.
ever move your stuff no always at least
언제나 당신의 물건을 항상 움직여야합니다.
coffee don't just move or replace also
커피도 그냥 움직이거나 교체하지 마십시오.
Garvey was saying that carbonite is a
Garvey는 카보나이트가
nice and secure or you can use Amazon
좋고 안전하거나 아마존을 사용할 수 있습니다.
ec2 service and it builds up a backup
ec2 서비스 및 백업을 구축합니다 .
set up there as well oh yeah I feel like
오, 그래, 거기에 설정도 같은 느낌
an s3 account or something and you could
s3 계정이나 뭔가 그리고 당신 수 있습니다.
save your stuff but that's that's again
물건을 저장하지만 그게 또 있습니다.
looking at cloud storage and things yeah
구름 스토리지 및 물건 예보고
yeah so I hope if anything that you
그래 그래서 나는 희망 아무것도 그 경우 당신
understand tonight that we need them you
오늘 밤 우리가 너에게 필요하다는 걸 이해해.
need to have more than one copy if you
당신이 원한다면 하나 이상의 사본이 있어야합니다.
have anything on your systems that is
너의 시스템에 뭐든지 가지고있어.
important to you I think of family
너에게 중요한 나는 가족을 생각한다.
photos make sure you copy them tonight
사진은 오늘 밤에 복사해야합니다.
to another hard drive and if you don't
다른 하드 드라이브로 이동하십시오.
have another hard drive and you've got a
다른 하드 드라이브가 있고
laptop at home do some kind of
집에서 노트북은 어떤 종류의 일을한다.
fandangled thing and copy don't move
어리석은 일과 사본은 움직이지 않는다.
copy that stuff over to that laptop so
그 물건 을 그 노트북에 복사해라.
that if something happens to your
만약 네 일이 생기면
computer you've got an extra copy and
컴퓨터에 여분의 복사본이 있고
then don't let anyone steal your laptop
랩톱을 훔치지 마라.
no yeah all right we're just we're
괜찮아, 우린 그냥 우리 야.
practically out of time here oh I we're
실은 시간이 없다.
running on a solid state drive tonight I
오늘 솔리드 스테이트 드라이브에서 뛰고 있습니다.
put a solid state drive into the server
서버에 솔리드 스테이트 드라이브를 넣어
which is very very cool it runs at five
그것은 매우 시원하다 그것은 5시에 달린다.
hundred and fifty five megabytes per
1 백 50 메가 바이트 당
second read and 515 right but one of the
두 번째 읽고 (515)를 잘하지만 중 하나
things that we're working on because
우리가 있기 때문에 작업중인 것들
we've got the cottage special coming up
우리는 오두막 특별오고 있어
next Tuesday night mm-hmm we're going to
다음 화요일 밤 mm-hmm 우리가 갈거야 .
be in haliburton Ontario and hope that
온다 리오 온타리오 에 있으니
you can join us there we've got lots of
거기에 우리와 함께 할 수 있습니다.
great prizes sponsored by Ellie I
Ellie I가 후원하는 훌륭한 상
electronics and just thrilled to have
전자 제품과
them as a part of it we're going to be
우리는 그것들 의 일부로서 우리가 될 것입니다.
there we've got live music with Eric kid
거기 에릭 아이와 함께 라이브 음악 있어요.
and it's just gonna be a great time with
멋진 시간이 될 것입니다.
our cottage special this here looking
우리 코티지 특별 찾고 여기
forward to being at Silver Beach
실버 비치에있는 것 앞으로
developments with Jerry
Jerry와의 개발
again this here you remember Jerry
다시 여기, 제리를 기억해.
Kowalski from last year so as part of
작년부터 Kowalski의 일원으로
that we needed to make the server
우리 가 서버를 만드는 데 필요한
portable you'll see in my blog bald nerd
내 블로그에서 볼 수있는 휴대용 대머리
calm that we really needed to make that
우리가 정말로 필요로 했던 진정
server portable because I had five of
내가 다섯을 가졌기 때문에 이식 가능한 서버
these bad boys big ol heavy hard drives
이 나쁜 남자들은 무거운 하드 드라이브
you can feel the way to that it's it's
당신은 그것이 그것이라고 느낄 수 있습니다.
awfully heavy five of five of them
5 명 중 5 명은 무겁게 무겁다.
that's like a whole bag I don't like a
그건 내가 좋아하지 않는 가방 전체 같아.
laptop these are enterprise drives that
노트북 이들은 엔터프라이즈 드라이브입니다.
were in to raid zeros I've got a weight
내가 제임스를 습격했다.
scale here here we go let's see ok we're
여기서 규모를 조정 해 보겠습니다.
going to reset that the weight is 656
체중이 656 인 것을 재설정하려고합니다.
grams so five of those is almost three
그 중 5 개가 거의 3 개입니다.
and a half kilograms somewhere in around
그리고 어딘가에서 반 킬로그램
there a little bit more than 30 matches
30 개 이상의 경기 가 조금있다.
this is like light is not its home it
이것은 빛이 집에 없다는 것과 같다.
literally it's like it could be in there
말 그대로 그것은 거기에있을 수있는 것 같아요.
and you wouldn't know the difference
그 차이를 알지 못할거야.
there they weigh nothing and no moving
거기서 그들은 무게가 나가고 움직이지 않습니다.
parts that's the key thing so that we've
중요한 부분이므로
cut down the weight but we've also
체중을 줄 였지만 우리는 또한
reduced the this was my concern is
내 관심사가 줄어들었다.
jostling during move movements so we
우리가 움직 이도록 움직이는 동안
have the kind of special next week we've
우리가했습니다 특별 다음 주의 종류가
got the fifth anniversary party on the
5 주년 기념 파티가 열렸어 .
twenty-fifth of September and of course
9 월 25 일과 물론
we're moving into our new studio before
우리는 이전에 새로운 스튜디오로 이전하고 있습니다.
that time August 27th I believe it is
그 시간 8 월 27 일 나는 그것이라고 믿는다.
that will be the new studio that's what
그것은 새로운 스튜디오가 될 것입니다.
I check check the calendar at category 5
카테고리 5 의 캘린더를 확인합니다.
TV yeah Oh is confident so that's where
TV 오 , 오, 자신감이 넘 칩니다 .
we're at hey thanks everybody for being
우리는 모두에게 감사합니다.
here Erica thank you for being here no
여기 에리카, 네가 여기있는 걸 고맙다.
problem it's nice to go away from Cod's
문제 는 Cod 's에서 벗어나는 것이 좋다.
country back in the Barry yeah yeah and
배리 예 나라에 다시 나라
here I go on my way out so see you from
여기에서 나는 밖으로 나의 길을 갈에서 당신을보고
halliburton Ontario next Tuesday night
Halliburton 온타리오 다음 화요일 밤
make sure you join us live and of course
우리 와 함께 살고 있는지 확인하십시오.
if you are in haliburton make sure you
당신이 할리 버튼에 있다면 당신이
join us in studio at we call it in
스튜디오에서 우리와 함께 하자.
studio but at Silver Beach developments
스튜디오가 아니라 실버 비치 개발
we've got lots of prizes to give away
우리는 많은 상을주고 있습니다.
we're looking forward to having you
우리는 당신 을 갖는 것을 고대하고 있습니다.
there's our studio audience and again
우리 스튜디오 관객이 있고 또
Eric kid is going to be there with me co
에릭 아이가 나와 함께 할거야.
hosting and performing live music as
라이브 음악 호스팅 및 공연
well so I'm a great time yeah it's going
잘 그래서 나는 좋은 시간예요 그것은 가고 있습니다.
to be fun so looking forward to it I am
재미 있기 때문에 기대하고 있습니다.
going to be a little bit more tanned a
조금 더 검게 될거야 .
little bit more relaxed I'll never beat
조금 더 편안하게 나는 결코 패배하지 않을거야.
end and I'll be a little bit more
끝나고 조금 더있을거야.
I cookin there you go take care everyone
내가 거기서 요리 하면 너는 모두를 돌봐야 해.
have a fantastic week we'll see you
우리가 너를 만날 환상적인 주간을 보내라.
later yeah
나중에 예